"iOS语言Key(勿动)" = "统一后英语";
"host_tips_msg" = "Your Team has been created, and it is now being displayed on the front page. Players are on their way. You can invite your friends to join your Team too.";
"more_traffic_detail_desc" = "Your stream will appear on the ePal main page, community, and profile page.";
"alert_title_double_check" = "Your post will not be saved";
"comment_score_desc_x" = "Your overall review rating for this service is %@";
"unpaid_desc_x" = "Your order will be cancelled in %@ if it is not paid";
"tips_no_network" = "Your network is unstable, please try again";
"toast_img_error_upload" = "Your image failed to upload, please try again";
"notice_title_epal_online" = "Your ePal just came online!";
"contact_information" = "Your Contact Information";
"your_buff_balance_is" = "Your Buff Balance:";
"alert_desc_balance_is_insufficient" = "Your buff balance is insufficient, please recharge";
"pending_for_review_desc" = "Your application will be reviewed in 2 business days, thank you for  your patience ";
"toast_remote_login" = "Your account has logged in from another location";
"alert_desc_log_another" = "Your account has been logged in on another device";
"recharge_time_notice" = "You will receive an additional prize worth of $300 for each monthly accumulative recharge, Bonus Buff does not count";
"wallet_guide_3" = "You will receive an additional prize worth of $300 for each monthly accumulative recharge";
"alert_desc_kick_out" = "You were kicked off line";
"empty_desc_instant_list" = "You should be the first one!";
"receive_2_buff_coupon" = "You received a coupon for 2 Buff (USD)";
"notice_desc_epal_online" = "You ordered “%@” with them recently";
"need_least_one_game" = "You need to have at least one game selected";
"hint_introduce_1" = "You need at least 10 characters here";
"alert_desc_comment_4stars" = "You must leave a comment when the review is below 4 stars. This would greatly help us to improve our service.";
"epal_apply_should_i_do" = "You might be thinking: “What should I do now?” Don’t worry, we have everything prepared for you";
"you_levelled_up" = "You Levelled Up!";
"you_have_received_x" = "You have received %@";
"hint_bind_email" = "You have not bound an Email";
"hint_bind_phone" = "You have not bound a Phone";
"hint_set_service_online" = "You have no service online, please set online first.";
"finish_x_order_gift" = "You have finished %@ paying orders on E-Pal, we hope you continue to meet interesting people!";
"alert_msg_room_kicked" = "You have been kicked from the Room";
"toast_kicked" = "You have been kicked and cannot enter this Room now";
"toast_blocked" = "You have been blacklisted and cannot enter this Room";
"you_have_a_call" = "You have a call";
"you_have" = "You have";
"alert_desc_an_expired_order" = "You had an expired order. If another order expires after 15 minutes, we will turn on the “Not accepting orders” toggle automatically.";
"notice_title_new_order" = "You Got A New Order!";
"forgot_check_agreement" = "You forgot to check the agreement";
"no_message_desc" = "You don’t have any messages";
"im_tips_black" = "You cannot complete this operation because he/she has blocked you";
"empty_desc_no_match" = "You can try to find clients through other E-Pal features";
"subscribe_epal_how_desc" = "You can subscribe to ePals through their profile";
"alert_desc_refund" = "You can refund the customer within 72 hours after the order is completed. If continue, the review of this order will be deleted, and the ePal Rating points may decrease. Do you confirm to continue？";
"you_can_visit_profile_if_they_see_you_too" = "You can only visit their profile if they checked out your eMeow too.";
"error_only_use_one_coupon_or_discount_code" = "You can only use one Coupon or Discount code";
"toast_img_error_count9" = "You can only upload up to 9 pictures in one topics";
"comment_only_upload_6pictures" = "You can only upload 6 pictures";
"toast_select_tags_only_3" = "You can only select up to 3 styles";
"alert_desc_gender" = "You can only edit your Gender once";
"alert_desc_age" = "You can only edit your Age once";
"block_list_desc" = "You can manage the blocked users here, such as removing them from the list.";
"notice_first_free" = "You can limit the number of free orders you provide each day, and the number will replenish at midnight of each day.";
"tips_gift_orders_to_friends" = "You can gift orders to your friends";
"wallet_guide_2" = "You can enjoy 1 recharge benefit for each option every Friday PST.";
"im_limit_tips_0" = "You can continue the conversation after receiving a reply. Or unlock unlimited messages by completing at least one of the following :";
"new_epal_alert_notice_to_bind_phone" = "You can now bind your phone number to get real-time order notifications";
"im_bottom_pending_buyer" = "You can always message the ePal again if they didn’t accpet the order. They might have missed your message.";
"toast_offline_by_manager" = "You are suspended from Room for %@ minutes. You won’t be able to start a room.";
"toast_suspende_team_find_details_msg" = "You are suspended from Room %@, please find more details in the system messages.";
"epal_apply_success_tips" = "You are now officially a part of the ePal community. You will join our 100,000+ ePals to showcase yourself to the world!";
"alert_desc_invite_mic_by_anchor" = "You are invited to join the voice chat";
"yesterday" = "Yesterday";
"yes" = "Yes";
"hint_bio" = "Write a short bio to introduce yourself";
"empty_desc_there_is_nothing_here" = "Wow, there is nothing here";
"nobody_is_here" = "Wow, nobody is here";
"im_send_x_game" = "Would you want to have a %@ game with me？";
"meet_invite_x" = "Would you like to play %@ with me?";
"worked_with_x" = "Worked with %@";
"free_order_desc_4" = "within 24 hours, your first order free will be disabled for 72 hours.";
"legends_why_title" = "Why verify for Legends";
"become_epal_why_title" = "Why become an ePal";
"become_epal_who_title" = "Who can be an ePal？";
"alert_desc_deactivate" = "When deactivated, players will not be able to subscribe to you, subscribed players will not be affected. Confirm to deactivate?";
"anonymous_epal_leaderboard_desc" = "When activated, you’ll not be shown on the ePal leaderboard.";
"anonymous_client_leaderboard_desc" = "When activated, you’ll not be shown on the Client leaderboard.";
"turn_off_suggestions_desc" = "When activated, the system won’t suggest you to anyone";
"become_epal_what_title" = "What's an ePal?";
"what_influencer" = "What is the Influencer Project?";
"what_do_you_get" = "What do you get?";
"post_instant_card_input_title" = "What do you feel like doing?";
"legends_what_title" = "What are Legends?";
"influencer_drive_desc_0" = "We'll do our best to drive views and viewers to your content.";
"welcoming_gift" = "Welcoming Gift";
"game_room_audience_tips_msg" = "Welcome to the Team for %@ has come,please update your in-game ID and get started!";
"welcome_epal" = "Welcome to \nE-Pal";
"chat_room_audience_tips_msg" = "Welcome to %@’s Team. You can join the Team voice chat here, jump on the Mic to start";
"welcoming_gift_will_expire_x_date" = "Welcome Gift will expire on %@, don't miss out.";
"welcoming_gift_expired" = "Welcome Gift has expired";
"desc_send_code_to_your_phone" = "We will send a verification code to the phone you entered";
"desc_send_code_to_your_email" = "We will send a verification code email to the email address you entered";
"toast_report_success" = "We will respond within 3 business days using the provided Email";
"influencer_paying_desc" = "We provide cash bonus from $200 to $2000 to our top performing influencers and content creators each month! Join our Discord community and contact officials for details.";
"influencer_creation_desc" = "We made a guidebook on how to make E-Pal-Related content. Hope it helps!";
"what_influencer_desc" = "We help content creators monetize their content and sustain themselve, while also generating content and attracting more followers";
"alert_desc_two_expired_order" = "We have turned on the \"Not accepting orders\" toggle for you because you had two expired orders";
"influencer_drive_title" = "We Drive Traffic to Your Content";
"epal_support_video_platform_paste_it" = "We currently support videos from YouTube, Twitch, and TikTok. Copy the video link to this box to connect it.";
"legends_what_desc_8" = "We are currently offering the Legends status for the following 9 games";
"legends_what_desc_x" = "We are currently offering the Legends status for the following %@ games";
"warning_you_are_leaving_epal_to_url" = "You are now leaving E-Pal";
"warning" = "Warning";
"legends_become" = "Want to become a Legend too?";
"wallet" = "Wallet";
"tips_call_wait_pick" = "Waiting for them to pick up the call";
"im_order_pending_buyer" = "Waiting for the ePal to accept the order";
"vote" = "Vote";
"volume" = "Volume";
"voice_record_rating" = "Voice recording rating";
"voice_recording" = "Voice Recording";
"tips_voice_failed" = "Voice Record upload failed, please submit again";
"voice_rating" = "Voice Rating";
"tips_voice_long" = "Voice line must be longer than 3s";
"tips_voice_used" = "Voice chat can only be used within 3 hours after the order is accepted or follow each other";
"visits" = "Visits";
"visitors" = "Visitors";
"client_title_visit" = "Visited Clients";
"vip_service" = "VIP Service";
"avatar_vip_gif_desc" = "VIP can use GIF profile photo";
"views" = "views";
"profile_im_desc" = "View their profile";
"view_more_arrow" = "View More >";
"tips_video_failed" = "Video upload failed, please submit again";
"video" = "Video";
"share_topic" = "Vibe together on E-Pal\nPlay Games, Meet Friends";
"very_delayed" = "Very Delayed";
"legends_verifi_now_arrow" = "Verify To Be A Legend Now! >";
"verify_now" = "Verify Now";
"verification_code" = "Verification code";
"legend_verification_desc" = "Verification | Super Exposure | Higher Service Price";
"value_of_orders" = "Value of Orders";
"alert_desc_legends_what_7_8" = "Immortal3, Radiant";
"valid_until" = "Valid until";
"valid_72_hour" = "Valid for 72 hours";
"vaild_for_7_days" = "Vaild for 7 days";
"at_least_18_age" = "Users must be at least 18 years old to register as an ePal.";
"alert_desc_activation" = "Users can subscribe to you on your personal page now!";
"users" = "Users";
"user_rating" = "User Rating";
"user" = "User";
"used_up" = "Used Up";
"use_eye_catching_introduce" = "Use an eye-catching one-liner to gain potential clients, 10 character minimum";
"use" = "Use";
"uploading" = "Uploading";
"uploading_video_post_will_get" = "Upload your gaming videos in the Community as an ePal will increase your orders.";
"skills_desc" = "Upload screenshots or videos of your games/services to showcase your skills";
"upload_failed" = "Upload Failed";
"voice_recording_desc" = "Upload a 15-second recording of your services introduction in English";
"update_now" = "Update Now";
"update_log" = "Update Log";
"update" = "Update";
"toast_internet_23G" = "Unstable mobile network detected";
"unpin_post" = "Unpin from your profile";
"unpaid" = "Unpaid";
"unmute_mic" = "Unmute Mic";
"alert_desc_emoji" = "Unlock it through eMeow draws";
"unlimited_chats" = "Unlimited Chats";
"unknown_singer" = "Unknown Singer";
"unit_total" = "units total";
"units" = "Units";
"unit" = "Unit";
"unfilled" = "Unfilled";
"under_review" = "Under Review";
"unblock" = "Unblock";
"toast_unbind_succeed" = "Unbind Succeed";
"alert_title_unbind_phone" = "Unbind Phone";
"alert_title_unbind_email" = "Unbind Email";
"unbind" = "Unbind";
"in_an_order_desc" = "Unavailable to take orders, but you can still send messages";
"empty_desc_unable_to_load_connected" = "Unable to load connected";
"type" = "Type";
"twitch_panel" = "Twitch Panel";
"twitch_service_card" = "Twitch E-Pal service card";
"twitch_epal_card" = "Twitch E-Pal Card";
"turn_off_suggestions" = "Turn Off Suggestions";
"try_reply_interesting_msg" = "Try to reply with interesting messages";
"try_other_keywrods_please" = "Try other keywords please";
"try_now" = "Try Now";
"transcendent" = "Transcendent";
"total" = "Total";
"topics" = "Topics";
"topic_content" = "Topic Content";
"influencer_perform_title" = "Top Performing E-Pal Videos";
"top_epals" = "Top ePals";
"top_client" = "Top Client";
"top_50" = "Top 50";
"top_100" = "Top 100";
"today" = "Today";
"empty_desc_potentail_44" = "To Team >";
"empty_desc_potentail_22" = "To Post >";
"empty_desc_potentail_33" = "To Instant >";
"toast_comment_less_10char" = "To help us better understand the order, please write at least 10 characters";
"insufficient_energy_desc" = "To feed %@, you’ll need %@ev, which can be gained by collecting your/someone else's energy.";
"free_order_desc_1" = "To build up your client base, you need to provide the same high quality services and response time regardless whether if the order is paid or free.";
"to" = "To";
"title_option" = "Title (Optional)";
"title" = "Title";
"tips_:" = "Tips:";
"tips" = "Tips";
"tip_center" = "Tip Center";
"tip" = "Tip";
"limit_recharge" = "Time-limited Recharge";
"time_limited" = "Time-Limited";
"time_zone" = "Time Zone";
"time" = "Time";
"this_week" = "This Week";
"tips_user_blocked_you" = "This user has blocked you";
"toast_game_start" = "This Room is now playing, please check out other Rooms";
"inpu_introduce_desc" = "This sentence will show up on your service profile page";
"cover_intro_desc" = "This sentence will be shown on the ePal list";
"tips_link" = "This link leads to outside of E-Pal, please be cautious";
"toast_img_error_5m" = "This image exceeds 5MB";
"link_copy_suceess" = "This game is not online, cannot be shared";
"the_food_been_fed" = "This food has been fed";
"tips_epal_status_x_may_not_response_time" = "This ePal's current status is %@, and may not be able to respond on time.";
"this_epal_is_offline" = "This ePal is offline";
"tips_epal_not_accept_order_now" = "This ePal is not accepting orders at the moment, no order can be placed";
"this_epal_not_accept_order_now" = "This ePal is not accepting orders at the moment";
"error_epal_disable_subscription" = "This ePal hasn’t enabled Subscription";
"alert_title_emoji" = "This Emoji is locked";
"tips_account_be_frozen" = "This account has been frozen due to violation of the platforms’s guidlines.";
"tips_bind_phone_success" = "This account has been bound";
"call_ignore" = "They ignored the call";
"empty_title_no_medals" = "They have no medals";
"call_hange_up" = "They hanged up";
"empty_they_dont_provide_services" = "They don't provide any services yet";
"call_not_pick" = "They did not pick up";
"call_cancel" = "They canceled";
"no_service_add_one_to_play_withother" = "There is no service yet, add a service and play with others";
"no_photos_subtitle" = "There is no photo here";
"empty_leaderboard" = "There is no one in this Leaderboard";
"empty_desc_no_service" = "There is no game yet, add a game and play with others";
"toast_no_host" = "There is currently no host";
"toast_no_open_mic" = "There are no open mic spots";
"toast_no_purchase_version" = "There are currently no items available for purchase in this version";
"theme" = "Theme";
"their_services" = "Their Services";
"toast_cannot_follow_self" = "The user you wish to gift has already left the Room";
"user_remove_from_list" = "The user has been removed from the block list.";
"user_not_exist" = "The user does not exist";
"subscribe_term_desc" = "The subscription fees will be automatically deducted through the %@ subscription service. %@ will renew the subscription at the end of your subscription. You can unsubscribe at any time by going to your Account Settings on %@. By subscribing, you agree to our platform’s Terms of Service, Privacy Policy and other agreements displayed.";
"the_stream_of" = "The stream of";
"share_epal_expired" = "The share bonus has expired";
"alert_desc_comment_no_auth" = "The review function is temporarily suspended on this account due to your recent actions";
"notice_price_range" = "The price range is 2.00 - 999.99";
"tips_call_overtime" = "The other party may not be able to pickup";
"toast_call_busy" = "The other party is busy, please try again later";
"pending_seller_desc_x" = "The order will be cancelled in %@ if you don’t accept it";
"pending_buyer_desc_x" = "The order will be cancelled in %@ if the order is not accepted by the ePal";
"pended_seller_cancel" = "The order was not accepted";
"unpaid_cancel_desc" = "The order has been canceled due to no payment";
"alert_content_help_rating_scores_part3" = "The number of services refers to the total completed gaming orders plus lifestyle orders.";
"match_desc" = "The Match is valid for 10 mins, please go chat with the client";
"the_list_is_empty" = "The List Is Empty";
"the_google_store" = "the Google Store";
"tips_not_support_message" = "The current version does not support the display of this message";
"toast_game_started_by_kicked" = "The current room is full, please check out other rooms.";
"alert_desc_apply_review" = "The content you changed must be reviewed. If you click Save, content related to this service will be reviewed. During this time, old service settings will not be affected. Do you confirm the changes?";
"toast_report_cancel" = "The content will not be saved after leaving, please confirm whether to leave";
"toast_comment_deleted" = "The comment has been deleted";
"im_order_first" = "The client might wish to order: %@";
"bing_phone_QA" = "The bound phone number is used to log in or receive order and other messages";
"bing_email_QA" = "The bound email is used to log in or receive order and other messages";
"alert_desc_average_order_accepting_time" = "The average order accepting time is %@ in the last 7 days.
PS: Order accepting time while your status is “Gaming”, “Resting” and “Offline” is not included.
Average order accepting time in the last 7 days is less or equal to 5 minutes - 6 Points, between 5 to 10 minutes - 3 Points";
"alert_content_help_rating_scores_part2" = "The average of these 4 aspects will become the final rating for this order. The average of all ratings received in the past 180 days will become the overall review rating for this service.";
"alert_content_rating_scores_less_than_10" = "The average of all ratings received in the past 180 days will become the overall review rating for this service.";
"alert_desc_average_im_response_time1_x" = "The average IM response time is %@ in the past 7 days.";
"notice_avg_im_response_time_equal_0" = "The average IM response time for the past 7 days is --, This user hasn’t been chatting recently";
"notice_avg_im_response_time_greaterthan_0" = "The average IM response time for the past 7 days is %@. This user responses had been %@";
"NSLocationWhenInUseUsageDescription" = "The approximate geographic location permission will be used to recommend players in the user's area";
"the_app_store" = "the App Store";
"empty_desc_user_not_exist" = "The account does not exist";
"review_passed_desc" = "The %@ you submitted has been approved.";
"terms_of_service" = "Terms of Service";
"alert_desc_legends_what_7_7" = "Grandmaster, Challenger";
"alert_desc_team_list" = "Team up with other online players through gaming and conversations now!";
"team_name" = "Team Name";
"no_team_desc_2" = "Team is a voice chat room for real-time team communication and interaction while gaming.";
"team_details" = "Team details";
"team" = "Team";
"tasks" = "Tasks";
"notice_desc_not_order" = "Talk to our staff to have them find your perfect ePal right now!";
"take_order" = "Take order";
"tags" = "Tags";
"tag_your_followers" = "Tag your followers";
"tag" = "Tag";
"anonymous_comments_desc" = "System will default to a 5-star rating if you do not give a review within 72 hours after the order has been completed";
"system_language" = "System Language";
"system" = "System";
"sync_your_stream" = "Sync your stream";
"sync_system" = "Sync with your system";
"switch" = "Switch";
"sure" = "Sure";
"summary" = "Summary";
"client_desc_suggestion" = "Suggestions for potential clients";
"suggestions" = "Suggestions";
"suggestion" = "Suggestion";
"toast_unpin_success" = "Successfully unpinned";
"toast_unfollow" = "Successfully Unfollowed";
"toast_pin_success" = "Successfully pinned";
"modify_success" = "Successfully modify";
"toast_follow" = "Successfully Followed";
"subtotal" = "Subtotal";
"subscriptions" = "Subscriptions";
"subscription" = "Subscription";
"subscribing" = "Subscribing";
"subscribers" = "Subscribers";
"subscribe_through" = "Subscribed to VIP through";
"tips_subscribe_success" = "Subscribed to VIP successfully";
"subscribed_successfully" = "Subscribed Successfully";
"subscribed_clients" = "Subscribed Clients";
"subscribed" = "Subscribed";
"subscribe_get_30_off" = "Subscribe: 30% Off";
"no_epal_subscription_desc" = "Subscribe to your favorite ePal and enjoy a 30% off on orders.";
"subscribe_to_vip" = "Subscribe to VIP";
"bubble_subscribe_epal_get_30_discount" = "Subscribe to this ePal and enjoy 30% off";
"email_subscriptions_desc" = "Subscribe to receive order notifications, news, major updates and promotional events";
"subscribe_epal_and_enjoy" = "Subscribe to ePal and Enjoy";
"subscribe_to_epal" = "Subscribe to ePal";
"subscribe_enjoy_30%_off" = "Subscribe to an ePal and enjoy 30% off on all orders";
"subscribe_now" = "Subscribe Now";
"subscribe" = "Subscribe";
"submit" = "Submit";
"styles" = "Styles";
"style" = "Style";
"tips_cancel_auth" = "Streamer Verification Removed";
"alert_title_streamer_paid_order" = "Streamer Paid Order Conversion Rewards";
"streamer" = "Streamer";
"tips_auth_success" = "Stream Connection Succeed";
"strategy" = "Strategy";
"store_rating" = "Store Rating";
"stop_matching" = "Stop Matching";
"still_need_help" = "Still Need Help?";
"step" = "Step";
"alert_title_steamer_follower" = "Steamer Follower Conversion Rewards";
"status" = "Status";
"no_conversations_desc" = "Starting chatting with ePals.";
"start_eapl_tutorial" = "Start the ePal tutorial now!";
"start_now" = "Start now";
"start" = "Start";
"more_traffic_desc" = "Special recommendations on the main page, community and profiles";
"special_banner" = "special banner";
"speaker" = "Speaker";
"sound" = "Sound";
"sort_by" = "Sort by";
"tips_you_cannot_buy_your_product" = "Sorry, you cannot purchase your own products.";
"sorry" = "Sorry";
"someone_subscribed_to_you" = "Someone subscribed to you in the past 7 days";
"social_media" = "Social Media";
"social" = "Social";
"slow" = "Slow";
"skip" = "Skip";
"skins" = "Skins";
"skills" = "Skills";
"skill_cover_rating" = "Skill Cover Rating";
"sliver" = "Silver";
"sign_up_with_twitch" = "Sign up with Twitch";
"sign_up_with_phone" = "Sign up with Phone";
"sign_up_with_google" = "Sign up with Google";
"sign_up_with_facebook" = "Sign up with Facebook";
"sign_up_with_email" = "Sign up with Email";
"sign_up_with_discord" = "Sign up with Discord";
"sign_up_with_apple" = "Sign up with Apple";
"sign_up_with" = "Sign up with";
"sign_up" = "Sign Up";
"sign_in_with_twitch" = "Sign in with Twitch";
"sign_in_with_phone" = "Sign in with Phone";
"sign_in_with_password" = "Sign in with password";
"sign_in_with_otp" = "Sign in with OTP";
"sign_in_with_google" = "Sign in with Google";
"sign_in_with_facebook" = "Sign in with Facebook";
"sign_in_with_email" = "Sign in with Email";
"sign_in_with_discord" = "Sign in with Discord";
"sign_in_with_apple" = "Sign in with Apple";
"sign_in_with" = "Sign in with";
"sign_in" = "Sign In";
"tabke_panel_subtitle" = "Showcase your E-Pal info on your Stream";
"twitch_epal_card_desc" = "Show your card overlay on your stream to attract viewers to order you";
"twitch_service_card_desc" = "Show your card on your stream information to attract viewers to order you";
"tip_please_reward_buff_to_epal" = "Show your appreciation to the ePal by leaving a tip";
"extension_subtitle_1" = "Show Tips and Follow button on your ePal Live page.";
"she_speak" = "She/he speaks";
"share_to_twitter" = "Shared to Twitter!";
"share_personal_page" = "Shared personal page in the last 3 days";
"share_by" = "shared by";
"shared_x_times" = "Shared %@ times";
"share_free_order_alert_desc" = "Share E-Pal with your friends to get first order free for both of you!";
"share_finish_order" = "Share E-Pal with anyone to get 2 Buff coupon for free (≧▽≦*)o";
"share_epal" = "Share E-Pal";
"share" = "Share";
"settings" = "Settings";
"setting_promotion" = "Setting Promotion";
"new_epal_guide_setp2" = "Setting discounts and promotions to enhance service competitiveness.";
"setting" = "Setting";
"set_your_password" = "Set your password";
"set_to_online" = "Set to Online";
"set_promotion" = "Set Promotion";
"hint_city" = "Set location permission";
"set_languages" = "Set Languages";
"set_it_up_now" = "Set it up now";
"set_avatar" = "Set Avatar";
"set_a_limit" = "Set a Limit";
"set_a_background" = "Set a background";
"services" = "Services";
"service_types" = "Service Types";
"notice_sevice_type_same" = "Service Type Cannot Be The Same";
"service_type" = "Service Type";
"service_review" = "Service Review";
"service_rating" = "Service Rating";
"service_name" = "Service Name";
"service_intro" = "Service Intro";
"service_info" = "Service Info";
"service_details" = "Service Details";
"service" = "Service";
"servers" = "Servers";
"hint_server_ranking_roles_etc" = "Server, ranking, roles etc.";
"server" = "Server";
"served" = "Served";
"subtitle_instant_last_ten_minutes" = "Send your requests to ePals, each request lasts for 10 minutes. Please check your IM for their messages";
"send_to" = "Send to";
"alert_desc_apply_legends_5" = "Our staff will help you to complete it from there.";
"send_successfully" = "Send successfully";
"send_otp" = "Send OTP";
"send_gift" = "Send Gift";
"audience_card_guide_title" = "Send Game Details";
"send_game_card" = "send Game Card";
"send_image" = "send an image";
"send" = "Send";
"sellers_orders" = "Seller's Orders";
"selected" = "Selected";
"hint_select_your_tags" = "Select your tags";
"hint_select_match_game" = "Select with games you want to receive matches for";
"toast_select_users" = "Select up to %@ users";
"select_unit" = "Select Unit";
"select_discount_title" = "Select the type of discounts";
"select_post_type" = "Select post type";
"buff_recharge_title" = "Select an option to recharge";
"title_service_cover" = "Select a Service Cover";
"select_a_service" = "Select a Service";
"select_a_game" = "Select a Game";
"select_a_friend" = "Select a Friend";
"select" = "Select";
"sec" = "Sec";
"hint_search_game_lifestyle" = "Search Game or Lifestyle services";
"search" = "Search";
"tips_screehot_failed" = "Screenshot upload failed, please submit again";
"screenshot_optional" = "Screenshot (Optional)";
"screenshot" = "Screenshot";
"notice_score_day" = "Scores of the last 180 days.";
"score" = "Score";
"score_player" = "Score";
"scan" = "Scan";
"hint_say_something" = "Say something...";
"save_your_banner" = "Save your special banner";
"save_suceessfully" = "Save successfully";
"save_succeed" = "Save succeed";
"save_error" = "Save error";
"alert_title_comment_back" = "Save Content";
"save" = "Save";
"rules" = "Rules";
"rule" = "Rule";
"room_topic" = "Room Topic";
"room_privacy" = "Room Privacy";
"room_name" = "Room Name";
"room_information" = "Room information";
"room_background" = "Room Background";
"role" = "Role";
"reward_issued" = "Rewards Issued";
"rewards" = "Rewards";
"toast_reward_send" = "Reward sent successfully";
"reward" = "Reward";
"reviews" = "Reviews";
"review_passed" = "Review Passed";
"review_failed" = "Review Failed";
"review" = "Review";
"retrieve_password" = "Retrieve Password";
"resting" = "Resting";
"responsiveness" = "Responsiveness";
"responsive" = "Responsive";
"response_time" = "Response Time";
"reset_password" = "Reset Password";
"reset" = "Reset";
"resend_seconds_x" = "Resend(%@ s)";
"resend_successful" = "Resend successfully";
"resend" = "Resend";
"rescan" = "Rescan";
"requirements" = "Requirements";
"report_im_desc" = "Report bad pictures/messages";
"report" = "Report";
"reply" = "Reply";
"renew" = "Renew";
"removed" = "Removed";
"remove" = "Remove";
"reload" = "Reload";
"voice_finish_record" = "Release to finish";
"reject" = "Reject";
"order_with_an_existing_client_QA" = "Regular Clients: Who has ordered you before. Finishing one order with a regular client get 2 points";
"registration_time" = "Registration Time";
"refunded" = "Refunded";
"refund" = "Refund";
"alert_desc_number_of_order_days" = "Refers to the number of order days in the past 7 days. Order days are the days you have completed at least 1 order. Each active day rewards you with 1 point.";
"alert_desc_number_of_active_days" = "Refers to the number of active days in the past 7 days. Each active day rewards you with 1 point, you can get up to 7 points per week.";
"recommended" = "Recommended";
"recommend" = "Recommend";
"epal_subscription_not_active_desc" = "Recive more income by having subscribers";
"toast_recharge_not_available" = "Recharge is not available, please try again later";
"recharge_x_buff" = "Recharge %@ Buff";
"recharge" = "Recharge";
"recent_exposures" = "Recent Exposures";
"recent" = "Recent";
"activity_notication_subtitle" = "Receive notifications when this ePal post on Live, Instant or Community";
"legends_why_desc" = "Receive more followers and opportunities for fan interactions.";
"receive_ev" = "Receive ev";
"epal_recommendation_desc" = "Receive ePals recommended by the platform";
"client_recommendation_desc" = "Receive clients recommended by the platform";
"ranking_desc" = "Receive a badge of honor when you are on the leaderboard";
"hint_contact_us" = "Reason for Reporting,Profile Link and ID if applicable.Note:Refund requests must include order ID number.";
"re_apply" = "Re-apply";
"alert_title_team_list" = "Real-time Team Voice Chat";
"read_all" = "Read All";
"cover_rule_title" = "Rating rules for cover image";
"voice_rule_title" = "Rating rules for audio recording";
"rating_criteria" = "Rating criterias:";
"rate_epal" = "Rate E-Pal";
"alert_title_legends_what_7" = "Rank Requirement";
"rank" = "Rank";
"high_quality_epals" = "Quality ePals";
"alert_desc_average_im_response_time3" = "PS: Only the first reply time from ePal after the buyer initiates the chat is counted.";
"promotion" = "Promotion";
"promo_code" = "Promo Code";
"profile" = "Profile";
"alert_desc_link_1" = "Proceeding may risk the exposure of your IP address, location, personal details and/or any type of harmful malware.";
"new_epal_guide_setp3" = "Proactively chat with clients to improve the of getting orders";
"prize_not_supoorsted" = "Prize system not supported.";
"prize_pool_instructions_arrow" = "Prize Pool and Instructions";
"privileges" = "Privileges";
"please_enter_password" = "Private Room, Please enter password";
"privacy_policy" = "Privacy Policy";
"privacy" = "Privacy";
"price_buff" = "Price(Buff)";
"price_settings" = "Price Settings";
"price_range" = "Price Range";
"price" = "Price";
"previous_period" = "Previous Period";
"preview" = "Preview";
"please_press_refresh_btn_right_top_corner" = "Press the refresh button at the top right corner";
"premium_discount" = "Premium Discount";
"potential" = "Potential";
"posts" = "Posts";
"posted_instant" = "Posted a “Instant” message in the past 3 days";
"posted_x_times" = "Posted %@ times";
"post_type" = "Post Type";
"alert_title_post_successful" = "Post Successful";
"post_my_instant_card" = "Post my Instant card";
"post_an_instant_card" = "Post an Instant Card";
"post" = "Post";
"positions" = "Positions";
"position" = "Position";
"influencer_popular_title" = "Popular Events";
"cover_exp_title_4" = "Poor";
"points_history" = "Points History";
"plus_discount" = "Plus Discount";
"list_cover_desc" = "Please upload your selfie here as the service cover image";
"cover_image_desc" = "Please upload a cover picture for your room.";
"upgradge_latest_version" = "Please upgrade to the latest version";
"update_app_try_again" = "Please update your App to try again";
"prize_not_supoorsted_update_to_see" = "Please update to see";
"im_order_finish_buyer" = "Please tip/review or issue a refund in 72 hours";
"toast_reward_error" = "Please tip 15 minutes after the order starts";
"please_sign_in_desc" = "Please Sign In";
"twitch_panel_desc_1" = "Please setup your E-Pal panel on Twitch profile to pass the review.";
"legends_how_desc_1" = "Send your application to Support@epal.gg";
"alert_desc_apply_legends_0" = "Please Send your application to Support@epal.gg";
"please_select_server" = "Please select your server";
"please_select_rank" = "Please select your rank";
"please_select_position" = "Please select your position";
"select_user_to_reward" = "Please select user to reward";
"toast_select_tags" = "Please select up to 3 tags.";
"hint_select_topics" = "Please select Topics";
"hint_select_discount" = "Please select the type of discounts";
"hint_select_language" = "Please select the language";
"toast_no_select_gift" = "Please select the item you'd like to gift";
"hint_select_style" = "Please select style";
"hint_select_server" = "Please select server";
"hint_select_report_type" = "Please select report type";
"hint_select_rank" = "Please select rank";
"hint_select_position" = "Please select position";
"hint_select_platform" = "Please select platform";
"hint_select_order" = "Please select Order ID";
"subtitle_enter_game_lifestyle_interested" = "Please select Games or Lifestyle services that you are interested in";
"room_background_desc" = "Please select an image as the background for your room.";
"toast_please_select_a_user_to_reward" = "Please select a user to reward";
"hint_select_service" = "Please select a service";
"please_select_a_game" = "Please select a game";
"please_select" = "Please select";
"im_order_finish_seller" = "Please review or issue a refund in 72 hours";
"toast_comment_error" = "Please review 15 minutes after the order starts";
"toast_no_microphone" = "Please open the microphone permission in the phone settings";
"user_rating_desc" = "Please make the review for this user, the review is anonymous.";
"toast_password_need_6_15_characters" = "Please make sure the password is 6 to 15 characters, and should contain numbers, uppercase and lowercase letters";
"alert_desc_bind_phone" = "Please link your phone number to continue.";
"kepp_least_1_game" = "Please keep at least 1 common game";
"please_insert_valid_links" = "Please insert valid links";
"please_insert_notes" = "Please insert notes.";
"hint_comment_input" = "Please insert at least 10 characters";
"please_input_title" = "Please input title";
"please_input_content" = "Please input content";
"legends_how_desc_3" = "Our staff will help you to complete it from there.";
"im_invite_x_feed_x" = "Please help me to feed my %@ with a %@";
"toast_tips_iap_purchase" = "Please go to the settings page to open IAP purchase";
"please_enter_dotdotdot" = "Please enter...";
"hint_enter_server" = "Please enter your service server";
"hint_enter_rank" = "Please enter your service rank";
"hint_enter_service_name" = "Please enter your service name";
"hint_user_rating" = "Please enter your review";
"hint_enter_phone" = "Please enter your phone number";
"hint_enter_password" = "Please enter your password";
"enter_the_otp" = "Please enter your OTP";
"hint_enter_nickname" = "Please enter your nickname";
"hint_name" = "Please enter your name";
"hint_enter_invitaion_code" = "Please enter your invitation code";
"hint_enter_gender" = "Please enter your gender";
"hint_enter_email" = "Please enter your email";
"please_enter_promo_code" = "Please enter Promo Code";
"social_media_desc" = "Please enter only social media links such as Facebook, Youtube, Instagram, TikTok, Twitch, Twitter, Discord, etc.";
"password_error_info" = "Please enter 6 to 15 characters";
"hint_enter_5_11_phone" = "Please enter 5-11 phone number";
"please_enter" = "Please enter";
"im_send_order" = "Please enjoy this prepaid gift order just for you.";
"dont_enter_repeated_links" = "Please don't enter repeated links";
"toast_mic_change" = "Please do not change locations frequently";
"query_help_for_invite_code" = "Please contact your registered friends on the platform and obtain an invitation code from the community event.";
"im_order_top_finish_seller" = "Please contact the customer to start service";
"im_order_top_finish_buyer" = "Please contact ePal to start service";
"alert_desc_unbind_phone_x" = "Please confirm whether to unbind the phone number %@";
"alert_desc_unbind_email_x" = "Please confirm whether to unbind the email %@";
"alert_desc_order_completed" = "Please confirm whether the service is complete.";
"empty_desc_music" = "Please confirm whether music files in MP3 format are stored in the phone";
"im_bottom_notpay_buyer" = "Please confirm order details with ePal before placing the order";
"alert_desc_delete_account" = "Please bind your phone number or email address to your account before you precede with this action";
"bind_phone_desc" = "Please bind your phone number before sending IM messages";
"tips_social" = "Please be careful when you give out off-platform accounts to ensure your safety";
"tips_pay" = "Please avoid off-platform transaction to protect your personal information";
"text_music_volume_desc" = "Please adjust the volume for the best vocal effect";
"hint_auto_reply" = "Please add your auto reply here";
"im_order_top_pending_seller" = "Please accept the order in 24 hours";
"empty_title_music_playlist" = "Playlist is empty";
"playlist" = "Playlist";
"room_host_guide" = "Players have joined your Team, click on their profile picture to invite them onto a mic";
"play_with_me" = "Play with me on epal.gg";
"play" = "Play";
"platinum" = "Platinum";
"platforms" = "Platforms";
"platform_agreements" = "Platform Agreements";
"platform" = "Platform";
"share_emeow_page" = "Plant kittens on E-Pal\nPlay Games, Meet Friends";
"place_order_anyway" = "Place Order Anyway";
"no_comments_subtitle" = "Place an order to write a comment";
"pin_post" = "Pin on your profile";
"photos_in_album≥2" = "Photos in Album ≥2";
"photos" = "Photos";
"photo" = "Photo";
"phone_verification" = "Phone Verification";
"phone" = "Phone";
"performance" = "Performance";
"notice_title_rcm_epal" = "Perfect ePal for you";
"per_day" = "Per Day";
"people_met" = "People Met";
"pending_for_review" = "Pending For Review";
"pending_buff_1" = "Pending Buff refers to your Buff income that is within the Security Period (3-15 days). They will be transferred to your account after this period.";
"pending_buff" = "Pending Buff";
"pending" = "Pending";
"peak_concurrent" = "Peak Concurrent";
"paypal" = "PayPal";
"payment_successful" = "Payment Successful";
"influencer_paying_title" = "Paying Sponsorship";
"pay" = "Pay";
"hint_paste_share_link" = "Paste YouTube, Twitch and Tiktok share link";
"past_7_days" = "Past 7 Days";
"past_30_days" = "Past 30 Days";
"edit_pwd_error" = "Password needs to be 6 digits long";
"toast_password_error" = "Password is incorrect, please try again";
"password" = "Password";
"share_room_text" = "Party up on E-Pal\nPlay Games, Meet Friends";
"alert_desc_legends_what_7_4" = "Grandmaster";
"monz_tool_desc" = "Overley, banner and other tools for streams";
"outfit_change_successful" = "Outfit Change Successful";
"outfit" = "Outfit";
"our_legends" = "Legends ePals";
"toast_rooms_is_full" = "Other room are full, please wait for other players to join or invite your friends to join your room";
"other_service_vocer" = "Other Service Cover Photos";
"other_language_stay_tuned" = "Other languages stay tuned";
"title_other_epals_play_this_game" = "Other ePals that play this game";
"other" = "Other";
"orders" = "Orders";
"client_title_order" = "Ordering Clients";
"ordering" = "Ordering";
"ordered_x" = "Ordered \"%@\" %@";
"ordered" = "Ordered";
"create_time" = "Order Time";
"order_message" = "Order Message";
"completed_dispute_desc" = "Order is being disputed, please wait for customer service or contact them now";
"order_id" = "Order ID";
"order_refunded" = "Order has been refunded";
"im_order_cancel" = "Order has been canceled";
"order_for_friends" = "Order for friends";
"im_order_top_dispute" = "Order disputed, please wait for customer service to resolve";
"order_days" = "Order Days";
"order_completion_time" = "Order Completion Time";
"order_acceptance_time" = "Order Acceptance Time";
"order" = "Order";
"or" = "Or";
"optional" = "Optional";
"opend_up_team" = "Opened up a Team in the past 3 days";
"opend_x_temes" = "Opened %@ times";
"open_original" = "Open Original";
"open_mic" = "Open Mic";
"search_game_epal_nodata" = "Oops…there is nothing here. Maybe try something else.";
"search_faq_nodata" = "Oops…there is nothing here. Maybe try a different keyword.";
"oops_there_is_nothing_here" = "Oops…there is nothing here";
"tips_no_epal_here" = "Oops…No pals here";
"oops_can_find_user_try_other_keyword" = "Oops...We can't find that user, Please try other keyword";
"empty_no_services_here" = "Oops...No service here";
"tips_no_connection" = "Oops, the connection seems broken, please try again later";
"oops_something_wrong" = "Oops, something went wrong!";
"empty_desc_searchimuser" = "Oops! We can’t find that user, \nplease try other keywords";
"empty_deleted_post" = "Oops! The topic is deleted by the author\r\nPlease browse other topics";
"empty_desc_comment_detail_not_exist" = "Oops! The comment is deleted by the author\r\nPlease browse other comments";
"points_history_desc" = "Only shows the points of the past four weeks";
"alert_desc_link_2" = "Only proceed with caution.";
"toast_avatar_error_estar2" = "Only eStar 2 could upload GIFs";
"toast_instant_create_error" = "Only 1 Instant card could be created at a time.";
"toast_select_error" = "Only %@ %@ can be selected";
"online_status" = "Online Status";
"online" = "Online";
"ongoing_order" = "Ongoing Order";
"original_password" = "Old Password";
"okay" = "Okay";
"ok" = "OK";
"offline" = "Offline";
"official" = "Official";
"off_mic" = "Off Mic";
"off" = "OFF";
"obtain" = "Obtain";
"number_of_orders" = "Number of Orders";
"number_of_order_days" = "Number of order days in the past 7 days";
"alert_title_number_of_order_days" = "Number of order days in the past 7 days";
"number_of_active_days" = "Number of active days in the past 7 days";
"alert_title_number_of_active_days" = "Number of active days in the past 7 days";
"skill_exp_desc4" = "NSFW text";
"yellow_photo_tip_upload_other" = "NSFW materials have been detected, please upload other photos";
"notification" = "Notification";
"notice" = "Notice";
"notes" = "Notes";
"buff_recharge_subtitle" = "Note: Buff recharged cannot be refunded";
"note" = "Note";
"not_yet_unlocked" = "Not yet unlocked";
"hint_no_select" = "Not selected";
"not_scored" = "not scored";
"not_recommend" = "NOT RECOMMEND";
"not_on_leaderboards" = "Not On Leaderboards";
"not_now" = "Not Now";
"not_installed" = "Not Installed";
"empty_no_following_epals" = "Not following any ePals";
"not_connect" = "Not connected";
"not_accepting_orders" = "Not Accepting Orders";
"normal_emojis" = "Normal Emojis";
"skill_exp_desc3" = "Non-game related image";
"panel_title" = "Non-ePal Exposure Panel";
"extension_title" = "Non-ePal Exposure Extension (on-site)";
"non_epal" = "Non-ePal";
"none" = "None";
"nonconforming" = "Nonconforming";
"nobody!" = "nobody!";
"toast_no_select_user" = "No users to give away";
"empty_title_transcation_history" = "No Transaction History";
"no_topics_yet" = "No topics yet~";
"no_team_desc_1" = "No Team available for %@, would you like to create one?";
"empty_title_no_team" = "No Team available";
"no_subscribers_yet" = "No Subscribers Yet";
"no_social_media" = "No Social Media Links Yet";
"skill_exp_desc2" = "No skill display - i.e. no level, rank, etc.";
"search_game_nodata" = "No services were found. Please try a different service";
"empty_no_services_found" = "No services found";
"no_service_online" = "No service online";
"no_service_no_fun" = "No service no fun";
"no_price_try_again" = "No prizes this time, give it another go!";
"empty_desc_potentail_1" = "No potential clients at the moment";
"no_photos" = "No Photos";
"no_other_info…" = "No other info…";
"empty_title_no_order_history" = "No Order History";
"no_notes_for_now" = "No notes for now";
"no_new_messages" = "No new messages";
"no_more_topics" = "No more topics~";
"no_more_instant_cards" = "No More Instant Cards";
"no_more_epals" = "No More ePals~";
"no_more_comments" = "No more comments～";
"no_more_available" = "No more available.";
"no_messages" = "No messages";
"no_message_now" = "No Message Now";
"no_match_found" = "No Match Found";
"empty_title_music" = "No local music available";
"empty_title_instant_list" = "No Instant card available";
"extension_subtitle_2" = "No installation is required, it will be shown while livestreaming.";
"no_information_available" = "No information available";
"no_history" = "No history";
"empty_desc_no_game_card" = "No Game Card Available";
"no_event_zone" = "No event zone";
"no_epals_availabel" = "No ePals Available";
"no_epal_subscription" = "No ePal Subscription";
"empty_no_comment" = "No discuss yet~";
"table_nodata" = "No Data";
"empty_desc_no_coupons_here" = "No coupons here.";
"no_conversations" = "No Conversations";
"no_comments" = "No Comments";
"no_available_coupons" = "No Available Coupons";
"no_auto_reply" = "No auto reply yet";
"empty_no_audience" = "No audience";
"no" = "No";
"nickname" = "Nickname";
"next_time" = "Next Time";
"contribution_timer_prefix" = "Next reset in";
"next" = "Next";
"newcomer_selfies" = "Newcomer Selfies";
"newcomer_gift" = "Newcomer Gift";
"wallet_guide_1" = "New users can enjoy 20% more Buff when recharging";
"new_user_exclusive_gifts" = "New User Exclusive Gifts";
"new_password" = "New Password";
"im_order_pending_seller" = "New Order";
"new_message" = "New Message";
"new_epals" = "New ePals";
"order_with_a_new_client_QA" = "New Clients: Who has never ordered you before. Finishing one order with a new client get 2 points";
"new" = "New";
"toast_internet_lost" = "Network connection lost, please check your internet connection";
"need_help" = "Need help?";
"name" = "Name";
"mythical" = "Mythical";
"my_subscriptions" = "My Subscriptions";
"my_subscription" = "My Subscription";
"my_stream" = "My Stream";
"my_store_rating" = "My Store Rating";
"my_store" = "My Store";
"my_services" = "My Services";
"my_rank" = "My Rank";
"my_phone_number" = "My Phone Number";
"my_orders" = "My Orders";
"my_medals" = "My Medals";
"my_links" = "My Links";
"my_epal_vip" = "My E-Pal VIP";
"my_coupons" = "My Coupons";
"my_clients" = "My Clients";
"my_business" = "My Business";
"mute_im_desc" = "Mute this user's message";
"mute_mic" = "Mute Mic";
"mute" = "Mute";
"music" = "Music";
"rule_multimedia_policy" = "Multimedia Policy";
"monz_tool" = "Monetization Tools";
"more_traffic" = "More Traffic";
"epal_subscription_incom_title" = "More subscription, more income";
"more_orders" = "More Orders";
"more_options" = "More Options";
"more_match_orders" = "More Match Orders";
"more_features" = "More Features";
"more_exposure" = "More Exposure";
"more_content" = "More Content";
"more" = "More";
"months" = "months";
"month" = "month";
"influencer_growing_desc" = "Monetization, Traffic, Content";
"toast_modify_success" = "Modify Successfully";
"cover_exp_title_3" = "Moderate";
"mins" = "mins";
"minimize" = "Minimize";
"min" = "min";
"toast_mic_closed" = "Mic is closed";
"mic_invite" = "Mic Invite";
"mic_number" = "Mic";
"resting_desc" = "Message notifications will be muted";
"message_clients" = "Message Clients";
"message" = "Message";
"alert_desc_instant_list" = "Meet like-minded gamers through exchanging Instant profile cards (last 30 minutes)";
"become_epal_friend_desc" = "Meet gamers from all over the world";
"share_profile" = "Meet gamers around the world\nPlay Games, Meet Friends";
"meet" = "Meet";
"medals" = "Medals";
"me" = "Me";
"empty_subtitle_try_another_filter" = "Maybe try again with different filters";
"matching_games" = "Matching Games";
"matching_completed" = "Matching Completed";
"matching_time" = "Matching";
"desc_matcted_epal_appear_in_im" = "Matched ePals will appear in your IM box.";
"toast_match_started_matched_appear_in_im" = "Match started. Matches ePals will appear in your IM box";
"match_settings" = "Match Settings";
"manage" = "Manage";
"male" = "Male";
"more_content_detail_desc" = "Make videos or stream E-Pal related content can help you attract fans quickly";
"make_friends" = "Make Friends";
"make_post" = "Make a post in the community in the last 3 days";
"lucky_draw" = "Lucky Draw";
"alert_desc_legends_what_7_9" = "Grandmaster, Challenger";
"log_out" = "Log Out";
"local_images" = "Local Images";
"sync_your_stream_desc" = "Livestream won't be synced to E-Pal when deactivated.";
"live_support" = "Live Support";
"live_epals" = "Live ePals";
"live" = "Live";
"tips_cover_failed" = "List Cover upload failed, please submit again";
"list_cover" = "List Cover";
"link_twitch" = "Link Twitch";
"line_busy" = "Line busy";
"likes" = "Likes";
"light_mode" = "Light Mode";
"skill_tips_title" = "Lifestyle Images/Videos:";
"lifestyle" = "Lifestyle";
"levels" = "Levels";
"level_up" = "Level up";
"lets_play_some_orders_now" = "Let's place some orders now!";
"empty_desc_transcation_history" = "Let's get the money flowing!";
"lets_get_some_orders_now" = "Let's get some orders now!";
"empty_desc_no_team" = "Let's create one now!";
"price_type_default" = "Let’s Play %@ Together!";
"legends_verification" = "Legends Verification";
"legends_title" = "LEGENDS ARE COMING !!!";
"legends" = "Legends";
"alert_desc_anchor_leave" = "Leaving the Team will cause the stream to end";
"leave" = "Leave";
"learn_influencer" = "Learn more about the Influencer Project";
"learn_more" = "Learn more";
"learn_more_influencer" = "Learn from more influencers";
"learn_epal" = "Learn about being an ePal";
"alert_desc_legends_what_7_1" = "Grandmaster, Challenger";
"leaderboard" = "Leaderboard";
"ranking" = "Leaderboard";
"latest" = "Latest";
"later" = "Later";
"last_sessions_top_contributor" = "Last session’s Top Contributor";
"languages" = "Languages";
"language_prepareing" = "language preparation";
"language" = "Language";
"alert_desc_room_kicke" = "Kick user from the current room?";
"toast_kick_success" = "kick success";
"kick" = "Kick";
"gotten_all_privileges" = "Keep it up, you have gotten all the exposure privileges.";
"privilege_exposures_desc" = "Keep it up, %@ privilege exposures awaits.";
"just_now" = "Just now";
"joined_the_room" = "Joined the room";
"joined_on" = "Joined on";
"joined" = "Joined";
"join_our_discord" = "Join our Discord";
"join_discord_epal" = "Join official discord server for ePals:";
"join_epal_now" = "Join E-Pal Now";
"join_community" = "Join Community";
"im_gift_tip" = "I've gifted you %@ * %@";
"its_great" = "It's great!";
"item" = "Item";
"seems_you_got_it_exchange_to_x_points" = "It seems that you've collected %@! The prize will be exchanged to %@ ev points.";
"empty_title_block_list" = "It Is Empty Here";
"iron" = "Iron";
"rewards_desc" = "Invite your friends to enjoy the promotion together";
"invite_users_to_mic" = "Invite users to mic";
"invite_members" = "Invite Members";
"invite_fans" = "Invite Fans";
"invite_code" = "Invite Code";
"invite" = "Invite";
"toast_invitation_successful" = "Invitation Successful";
"invitation_code_optional" = "Invitation Code (Optional)";
"invitation_code" = "Invitation Code";
"invitation" = "Invitation";
"toast_internet_error" = "Internet error";
"empty_desc_no_order_history" = "Interact in the Community tab and promote yourself on social medias to get orders!";
"toast_gift_count_insufficient" = "Insufficient gifts, please try again";
"insufficient_ev" = "Insufficient ev";
"insufficient_energy" = "Insufficient energy";
"alert_desc_post_successful" = "Instant cards will attract like-minded gamers. Please be patient and pay attention to your DM.";
"timer_instant_card_on_display_x" = "Instant card on display %@";
"alert_title_instant_list" = "Instant - Find Online Gamers";
"instant" = "Instant";
"accept_extension_subtitle_2" = "installation is required, it will be shown while livestreaming.";
"input_team_password" = "Input Room Password";
"placeholder_search_game_epals" = "Input Service, Name or ID";
"input_room_information" = "Input Room information";
"initiated_chats" = "Initiated chats with “My Clients” in the past 3 days";
"initiated_x_conversations" = "Initiated %@ conversations";
"toast_info_update" = "Information update succeed";
"Info" = "Info";
"influencer_tools" = "Influencer Tools";
"influencer_growing" = "Influencer Project";
"influencer" = "Influencer";
"incomplete" = "Incomplete";
"income_x" = "Income %@";
"income" = "Income";
"incognito_browsing" = "Incognito Browsing";
"in_progress" = "In Progress";
"in_an_order" = "In an Order";
"complete_your_profile_desc" = "Improving your profile is the first step to orders";
"complete_profile_desc" = "Improving your profile is the first step to orders";
"gain_more_subscriptions_desc" = "Improve your service quality to gain more subscriptions";
"improve_order_taking_ability" = "Improve order-taking ability, get more orders and with ZERO commission";
"epal_tips_desc" = "Improve order taking ability to get more orders";
"improve_now" = "Improve now";
"new_epal_guide_setp1" = "Improve ePal ratings, active ePal subscription and improve order taking skills.";
"image_video_guide" = "Images and Video Guidelines";
"image_send" = "image send";
"img_load_failed" = "Image load failed";
"cat_status_so_happy" = "I'm so happy!";
"im_settings" = "IM Settings";
"alert_desc_average_im_response_time2" = "IM response time is not included while your status is “Gaming”, “Resting” and “Offline”.";
"im_online_chat_with_me" = "I'm online, chat with me";
"im_message" = "IM Message";
"cat_status_feeling_unwell" = "I'm feeling unwell";
"cat_status_excited" = "I'm Excited";
"cat_status_chiling" = "I'm Chilling";
"ignored" = "Ignored";
"pending_buff_4" = "If you’ve completed over 50 orders, your Security Period would be 3 days.";
"pending_buff_2" = "If you’ve completed less than 20 orders, your Security Period would be 15 days.";
"pending_buff_3" = "If you’ve completed 20-49 orders, your Security Period would be 7 days.";
"completed_buyer_desc_x" = "If you’d like a refund, please contact the ePal directly. If there is any issues, please report in %@";
"free_order_desc_2" = "If you receive three";
"desc_recive_text_help_title" = "If you did not receive our text";
"desc_receive_email_help_title" = "If you did not receive our email";
"alert_desc_order_refund_accept" = "If you agree to a refund, the order amount will be returned in the method it was originally paid. Are you sure you want a refund?";
"not_accepting_orders_desc" = "If ticked, customers won’t be able to place orders with you";
"alert_desc_order_refund_reject" = "If the refund is declined, the customer may apply to the platform for arbitration. Are you sure you want to decline the refund?";
"im_bottom_pending_seller" = "If the order cannot be accepted, please kindly explain to your customer.";
"identity" = "Identity";
"cat_happy_if_complete_5_tasks" = "I'd be so happy if you could complete any 5 tasks";
"id" = "ID";
"im_buff_tip" = "I’ve gifted you %@ Buffs";
"its_great_desc" = "I’m glad you liked it!\r\n\r\nOur team would appreciate a rating in the App/Play store. Could you please show us some support? (つ´ω`)つ";
"cat_happy_if_feed_one_more" = "I will become Happy if you feed me 1 more time.";
"im_subscribe_you" = "I have just subscribed to you.";
"i_have_a_promo_code" = "I have a Promo Code";
"alert_content_title_improve_response_time" = "How to improve IM response time?";
"how_to_find_youtube_share_link" = "How to find Youtube share link?";
"how_to_find_the_share_lik" = "How to find the share link";
"accept_panel_title" = "How to customize my Panel?";
"how_to_build_card" = "How to build a E-Pal Card";
"legends_how_title" = "How to become a Legend ePal?";
"how_it_works" = "How it Works";
"epal_subscription_how_title" = "How does it work";
"how_help" = "How can we help?";
"influencer_how_title" = "HOW CAN WE HELP";
"hours" = "hours";
"hour" = "hour";
"hot" = "Hot";
"host" = "Host";
"voice_start_record" = "Hold to start";
"highlights" = "Highlights";
"become_epal_desc" = "High income · Flexible · Make Friends";
"high_income" = "High income";
"hide_birthday" = "Hide Birthday";
"share_service" = "Hi~guys, this is %@’s service in %@, click the picture to play with%@~";
"share_user_service_content" = "Hi~guys, this is %@’s service in %@, click the picture to play with %@~";
"share_user_profile_content" = "Hi~guys, this is %@’s profile in %@, click the picture to play with %@~";
"car_first_give_name_title" = "Hi hooman, could you give me a name?";
"im_ceo_free_coupon_x" = "Hi %@, thank you for using E-Pal for the first time! Share E-Pal with anyone to get 2 Buff coupon for free (≧▽≦*)o!";
"recommend_other_epal_to_you_order" = "here is an alternative online ePal, or you can continue to place the order anyway";
"help_center" = "Help Center";
"10000_influencer_desc" = "Have boosted their career through E-Pal";
"empty_subtitle_follow_other_to_access" = "Have an easy access to your Favorite ePals by following them";
"have_a_try" = "Have a try";
"msg_join" = "has entered the room";
"hanged_up" = "Hanged up";
"hang_up" = "Hang Up";
"order_with_an_existing_client" = "Had an order with an existing client in the last 7 days";
"order_with_a_new_client" = "Had an order with a new client in the last 7 days";
"guest" = "Guest";
"growing_project" = "Growing Project";
"got_it" = "Got it";
"customer_relations_desc" = "Good customer relations will lead to regular orders";
"cover_exp_title_2" = "Good";
"gold" = "Gold";
"go_setting" = "Go Setting";
"go_on" = "Go On";
"go_follow_meet_one" = "Go follow or meet someone new!";
"go" = "Go";
"give_up_edit" = "Give up Edit";
"give_up" = "Give Up";
"im_gift_coupon_x_buff" = "Gifted you a coupon for %@ Buff";
"toast_gift_order_sent" = "Gift Order Sent";
"git_order" = "Gift Order";
"gift_now" = "Gift Now >";
"gift_income_e-coins" = "Gift income Buff";
"gift_coupons" = "Gift Coupons";
"gift_buff" = "Gift Buff";
"gift" = "Gift";
"cat_status_get_disappointed" = "Getting disappointed";
"get_y" = "Get Y";
"get_it_now" = "Get it now";
"get_it" = "Get It";
"epal_level_desc" = "Get exposure and coupons by leveling up";
"start_level_up_get_emeows_cooler" = "Get even cooler eMeows by leveling up! Let's start now!";
"get_ev_arrow" = "Get ev";
"get_2_buff_coupon" = "Get 2 Buff Coupon";
"banner_personal_desc" = "Generate your own banner and unique link, which then can be used in your stream, and on your social media for orders from your fans.";
"general" = "General";
"gender" = "Gender";
"gears" = "Gears";
"gateway" = "Gateway";
"games" = "Games";
"game_team" = "Game Team";
"skill_intro_title" = "Game screenshots and Videos:";
"game_room" = "Game Room";
"game_info" = "Game Info";
"game_in_progress" = "Game in Progress";
"game_card_added" = "Game Card Added";
"game_card" = "Game Card";
"game" = "Game";
"store_rating_subscription_desc" = "Gain extra income when players subscribe to you";
"someone_subscribed_to_you_QA" = "Gain 5 points if you were subscribed by a client in the past 7 days";
"from" = "From";
"friends" = "Friends";
"frendliness" = "Friendliness";
"hint_free_order_count" = "Free orders you provide";
"free_order_epals" = "Free Order ePals";
"unlimited_chats_subtitle" = "Free communication with this ePal, no limits";
"alert_desc_legends_what_7_3" = "Grand Champion";
"forget_your_password" = "Forget your password?";
"for_you" = "For you";
"for_newcomer" = "For Newcomer";
"hint_introduce_2" = "For example:[LoL] I am a god in League, 1 free order for you if you beat me solo mid";
"for" = "For";
"following" = "Following";
"followers" = "Followers";
"followed_epals" = "Followed ePals";
"following_im_desc" = "Follow them now";
"follow" = "Follow";
"flexible" = "Flexible";
"finished" = "Finished";
"finish_task_grow_emeow_fast" = "Finish your tasks to grow your eMeow faster. Let's go!";
"finish" = "Finish";
"video_paste_help_desc" = "Find the video you want to share. Click the share button and find the link. Copy it, and paste it to E-Pal.";
"find_new_clients" = "Find new clients";
"empty_desc_floowing_List" = "Find ePal to follow in the Community and ePal tabs!";
"how_to_build_card_desc" = "Find E-Pal Card in the “Extensions” on Twitch, and install.";
"final_price" = "Final Price";
"filter_x" = "Filter(%@)";
"filter" = "Filter";
"desc_fill_your_code_in_box" = "Fill in the box with the verification code which was sent to";
"female" = "Female";
"cover_exp_desc_2" = "Feels natural, but facial features are partially obstructed, and the background is a little messy.";
"feeds" = "Feeds";
"feed_request" = "Feed Request";
"feed_now" = "Feed Now";
"feed" = "Feed";
"fed_by_x" = "Fed by %@";
"fed_by" = "Fed by";
"favorites" = "Favorites";
"favorite" = "Favorite";
"fast_review" = "Fast Review";
"fast" = "Fast";
"faq" = "FAQ";
"fans" = "Fans";
"toast_join_failed" = "Failed to join the Room, please try again";
"failed" = "Failed";
"expiry_date_x" = "Expiry Date: %@";
"expired" = "Expired";
"epal_points_rules_desc3" = "Expire orders means when ePal fails to respond to an order in 24 hours, thus resulting in the systematic cancellation of the order";
"expense_x" = "Expense %@";
"expand" = "Expand";
"exp" = "exp";
"client_title_existing" = "Existing Clients";
"rewards_tag" = "Exclusive to quality customers";
"skill_cover_rating_QA" = "Excellent - over 80 points - 8\nGood - 60-80 points - 4\nModerate - 40-60 points - 0\nPoor - less than 40 points - 0";
"voice_recording_QA" = "Excellent - over 80 points - 8\nGood - 60-80 points - 4\nModerate - 40-60 points - 0\nPoor - less than 40 points - 0";
"cover_exp_title_1" = "Excellent";
"skill_exp_title" = "Examples of good images & bad images";
"example_epal" = "Example ePals";
"more_content_desc" = "Examples of excellent perfomring content template";
"examples" = "Examples";
"example" = "Example";
"event_zone" = "Event Zone";
"event" = "Event";
"ev_production_reduced_to_0" = "Ev production is reduced to 0";
"v_production_reduced_to_x" = "Ev production is reduced by %@";
"get_more_ev_if_feed_one_more" = "Ev generated +%@, I'd become Excited if you feed me 1 more time.";
"get_more_ev_if_complete_x_tasks" = "Ev generated +%@, I'd become Excited if you complete %@ more tasks!";
"get_more_ev_x" = "Ev generated +%@";
"ev" = "ev";
"etx_xx_replys" = "etc %@ replys";
"epal_points_rules_desc2" = "eStars 1 and 2, privileges will remain for 1 and 2 weeks respectively even if the same levels are not reached in the next week.";
"estar" = "eStar";
"equipped" = "Equipped";
"equip" = "Equip";
"subscribe_epal_recmd" = "ePals you might like";
"become_epal_what_desc" = "ePals are freelancers who provide personalized gaming services";
"epals" = "ePals";
"epal_platform_polocy" = "Epal.gg is dedicated to creating a social gaming platform where users can safely and creatively express themselves. To reach this goal, please observe our Multimedia Policy when uploading images to your game application.These policies apply to all genders.";
"pended_buyer_cancel" = "ePal was busy, order was not accepted";
"epal_vip" = "E-Pal VIP";
"epal_types" = "ePal Types";
"epal_tips" = "ePal Tips";
"pending_buff_5" = "ePal Subscription: In order to ensure the client's subscription rights, the subscription service fee will be withdrawable to the ePal on a monthly basis.";
"epal_subscription_not_active" = "ePal Subscription not active";
"tips_deactivate_success" = "ePal Subscription deactivated";
"epal_subscription" = "ePal Subscription";
"epal_recommendation" = "ePal Recommendation";
"epal_promotion" = "ePal Promotion";
"epal_points_rules" = "ePal Points Rules";
"epal_points_rules_desc1" = "ePal points are calculated 2AM of every Monday (PST), qualified ePals will enjoy privilege exposures for the week.";
"sign_in_check_agreement_highlight" = "E-Pal Platform Terms of Service.";
"epal_signup_need_13yearsold" = "E-Pal platform forbids users under the age of 13 to register";
"tabke_panel_title" = "ePal Order Taking Panel";
"epal_order_extension" = "ePal Order Extension";
"accept_extension_title" = "ePal Order Accepting Extension (on-site)";
"epal_match" = "ePal Match";
"epal_level" = "ePal Level";
"legends_what_desc_0" = "E-Pal Legends should meet at least ONE of the following categories:";
"notice_title_not_order" = "ePal isn’t taking your orders?";
"about_us_desc" = "E-Pal is a social platform for gamers to make friends worldwide through playing video games";
"become_epal_about_desc" = "E-Pal is a social platform for gamers to make friends worldwide through playing video games";
"im_ceo_share" = "E-Pal is a brand new world of social interactions!";
"tips_nsfw" = "E-Pal does not allow any form of NSFW service, rule violation will result in account suspension";
"epal_buff" = "E-Pal Buff";
"epal" = "ePal";
"effect" = "Entrance Effect";
"hint_use_promo_code" = "Enter your promo code";
"enter_my_room" = "Enter my room";
"enjoyment" = "Enjoyment";
"enjoying_epal_so_far" = "Enjoying E-Pal so far?";
"enjoy_reduced_transaction" = "Enjoy reduced transaction fees when you reach %@ points";
"epal_vip_privilege" = "Enjoy %@ exclusive privileges";
"engagement" = "Engagement";
"ended" = "Ended";
"enabled" = "Enabled";
"enable_now" = "Enable Now";
"enable_auto_renew" = "Enable Auto Renew";
"empty" = "Empty";
"emeow_emojis" = "eMeow Emojis";
"emeow" = "eMeow";
"email_verification" = "Email Verification";
"email_subscriptions" = "Email Subscriptions";
"email_format_incorrect" = "E-mail format is incorrect";
"email" = "Email";
"hint_room_name" = "Edit Team name here";
"edit_service" = "Edit Service";
"edit_personal_information" = "Edit Profile";
"edit_profile" = "Edit Profile";
"edit_my_team" = "Edit my team";
"hint_cat_name" = "Edit eMeow's name";
"edit_avatar" = "Edit Avatar";
"edit_album" = "Edit Album";
"edit" = "Edit";
"become_epal_income_desc" = "Earn more than 5,000 USD per month while gaming";
"become_an_epal_desc" = "Earn extra cash by gaming with others";
"hint_social_media" = "E.g.,http://www.epal.gg/epal/1";
"hint_post_instant_card" = "e.g. I’m a college student from New York. I am a big fan of DND and Among Us, send me your favourite setup!";
"hint_price_type" = "e.g. Casual games, Ranked, Coaching";
"duration" = "Duration";
"draw_for_free" = "Draw for free";
"download_epal_content" = "Download E-Pal content guides";
"download_app" = "Download APP";
"dont_use_promocode" = "Don't use promo code";
"dont_have_acount" = "Don't have an account?";
"cover_exp_desc_4" = "Does not contain a real person, and it has no real content. It is unappealing.";
"notice_title_try_new" = "Do you want to try someone new?";
"alert_desc_log_out" = "Do you want to log out?";
"ask_give_up_your_edit" = "Do you want to give up edit?";
"alert_desc_delete_service" = "Do you want to delete this service?";
"tips_delete_photo" = "Do you want to delete this photo?";
"do_you_want_bind_existing_acount" = "Do you want to create a new account or bind an existing E-Pal account to your %@ account？";
"accept_extension_subtitle_1" = "Display buttons for tipping and ordering on your ePal Live page.";
"discussion" = "Discuss";
"discount" = "Discount";
"disabled" = "Disabled";
"disable_auto_renew" = "Disable Auto Renew";
"query_dont_receive_code" = "Didn’t receive code?";
"dismond" = "Diamond";
"details" = "Details";
"description" = "Description";
"alert_desc_delete_account_password_set" = "Deleting your account will remove all of your income and balance. If you have subscribed to VIP, you need to cancel it through your payment methods. ARE YOU SURE YOU WANT TO DELETE YOUR ACCOUNT?";
"toast_deleted_succeed" = "Deleted successfully";
"delete_message" = "Delete Message";
"delete_account" = "Delete Account";
"delete(x)" = "Delete (%@)";
"delete" = "Delete";
"free_order_desc_3" = "delayed response penalties";
"notice_free_order" = "Delay response penalty refers to when an ePal is “Online”, but failed to respond to an order request in 30 minutes. This will add 1 penalty to you, which displays a notice saying: This ePal may not be able to respond in time to clients who intend to place orders.";
"notice_free_order_title" = "Delay response penalty";
"legends_how_desc_2" = "Include the nickname you are commonly known for, your E-Pal ID or Account link, your in-game ID, and any social media accounts that would help us to verify you.";
"deactivate_epal_sub" = "Deactivate ePal Subscription";
"deactivate" = "Deactivate";
"dark_mode" = "Dark Mode";
"daily_tasks" = "Daily Tasks";
"customized" = "Customized";
"custom_something_want_say" = "Customize to something you want to say";
"customize" = "Customize";
"alert_desc_help_center" = "Customer service is currently offline, and will respond when we return. While you wait for us, please file a report.";
"customer_service" = "Customer Service";
"customer_relations" = "Customer Relations";
"custom_greeting" = "Custom Greeting";
"custom" = "Custom";
"toast_voice_channel_is_occupied" = "Currently using other voice communication services, please try again later";
"current_time" = "Current Time";
"current_subscribers" = "Current Subscribers";
"current_rating_points" = "Current Rating Points (To be settled)";
"current_rating" = "Current rating";
"current_privileges" = "Current Privileges";
"current_level" = "Current Level";
"no_message_title" = "Cuckoo, cuckoo...";
"alert_desc_legends_what_7_2" = "The Global Elite";
"creating_ev" = "Creating ev";
"influencer_desc" = "Create content about E-Pal and enjoy growth on views, followers and income! WE GOT YOU COVERED! Join our community and get the full support.";
"create_at" = "Create at";
"create_a_team" = "Create a Team";
"create_a_room" = "Create a room";
"create" = "Create";
"cover_rating" = "Cover Rating";
"cover_intro" = "Cover Intro";
"alert_cover_rating" = "Cover image rating";
"cover_voice_rating" = "Cover Image & Voice Rating";
"cover_image" = "Cover Image";
"coupons" = "Coupons";
"share_coupon_complete" = "Coupon from sharing has been credited";
"coupon" = "Coupon";
"could_be_better_desc" = "Could you please help us out and give us some love and support?\r\n\r\nYour suggestions will make E-Pal a better place.";
"could_be_better" = "Could be better";
"copy_your_link" = "Copy your link";
"tips_copy_success" = "Copy successful";
"copy" = "Copy";
"contribution" = "CONTRIBUTION";
"cheer_to_get_one_privilege" = "Continue to cheer, you can also get 1 Exposure Privilege.";
"continue" = "Continue";
"content_not_saved" = "Content Not Saved";
"alert_desc_comment_back" = "Content is not saved, do you want to leave?";
"influencer_creation_title" = "Content Creation Tutorial";
"content_optional" = "Content (Optional)";
"content" = "Content";
"contact_us" = "Contact Us";
"contact" = "Contact";
"share_free_order_content" = "Congrualations on receiving the first order for free, play with the ePals now!";
"alert_desc_your_paid_order" = "Congratulations! Your paid order conversion for this month is %@ ranked %@. Your reward is %@ Buff";
"alert_desc_your_follower" = "Congratulations! Your follower conversion for this month is %@, ranked %@. Your reward is %@ %@";
"congratulations_mark" = "Congratulations!";
"congratulations_x_buff_issued_to_wallet" = "Congratulations on winning %@. The Buff prize will be issued to your Wallet";
"congratulations" = "Congratulations";
"new_user_send_buff_prefix" = "Congrats! You received";
"alert_desc_delete_card" = "Confirm to delete this card?";
"confirm_subscription" = "Confirm Subscription";
"confirm_payment" = "Confirm Payment";
"confirm_order" = "Confirm Order";
"confirm" = "Confirm";
"completed" = "Completed";
"complete_your_profile" = "Complete your profile";
"complete_profile" = "Complete your profile";
"supplement_user_info_title" = "Complete Your Details To Meet Real Friends";
"complete" = "Complete";
"community_guidelines" = "Community Guidelines";
"community" = "Community";
"audience_card_guide_desc" = "Communicate your strategy for the game. You can also send your Game Card to showcase your Rank and skills";
"comment" = "Comment";
"coming_soon" = "COMING SOON";
"notice_desc_rcm" = "Come over and say Hi!";
"notice_desc_client_online" = "Come over and say Hi!";
"notice_desc_new_epal" = "Come over and say Hi!";
"share_emow_levelup" = "Come and join me on E-Pal to meet friends with the same interests. You can also win PS5, Nintendo Switch and many more prizes!";
"collectable" = "Collectable";
"collect_energy" = "Collect energy";
"collapse" = "Collapse";
"coach" = "Coach";
"close_mic" = "Close Mic";
"alert_content_help_rating_scores_part1" = "Clients will review each service in 4 aspects: response time, friendliness, in-game performance, and enjoyment.";
"client_desc_visit" = "Clients who visited, followed, chatted or tried to order";
"client_desc_subscribe" = "Clients who subscribed to you";
"client_desc_existing" = "Clients who have completed orders with you";
"client_desc_order" = "Clients on Match";
"clients" = "Clients";
"client_title_suggestion" = "Client Suggestions";
"client_recommendation" = "Client Recommendation";
"client_management" = "Client management";
"click_to_upload" = "Click to Upload";
"click_to_check" = "Click to Check";
"audience_mic_guide_desc" = "Click on available Mic spot to join voice chat";
"audience_mic_guide_title" = "Click on an empty Mic";
"cover_exp_desc_1" = "Clean background, and well-defined facial features. This is a great portrait.";
"claimed" = "Claimed";
"claim" = "Claim";
"city" = "City";
"choose_a_service" = "Choose a Service";
"choose" = "Choose";
"chit_chat" = "Chit-Chat";
"check_legend" = "Check out the Legend Verification";
"legends_desc" = "Check out the Gaming Legends on E-Pal, they are the most engaging gamers, creators and professional players you can ever find!";
"notice_desc_try_new" = "Check out our newly approved ePals";
"check_out" = "Check Out";
"check_order" = "Check Order";
"check_more" = "Check More";
"check" = "Check";
"chat..." = "Chat...";
"chat_with_your_epal" = "Chat with your ePal";
"tips_call_notice" = "Chat with the player via Voice Call";
"chat_room" = "Chat Room";
"chat" = "Chat";
"chart" = "Chart";
"alert_desc_name_input_empty" = "Changes will not be saved if you leave now";
"change_saved" = "Changes Saved";
"toast_change_succeed" = "Changed Succeed";
"change_password" = "Change Password";
"change_avatar" = "Change Avatar";
"change" = "Change";
"certifications" = "Certifications";
"card" = "Card";
"now_view_order" = "Can't view the order";
"tips_blank_message" = "Can't send blank message";
"toast_connot_enter_other_room" = "Cannot enter other rooms during live broadcast";
"canceled" = "Canceled";
"cancel_authorize" = "Cancel Authorize";
"cancel" = "Cancel";
"toast_not_open_mailbox" = "Can not open mailbox";
"tips_no_discord" = "Can not open Discord";
"call_to_start" = "Call To Start";
"call_time" = "Call Time";
"alert_desc_legends_what_7_6" = "Master, Grandmaster, Challenger";
"call_duration" = "Call duration";
"call" = "Call";
"buyers_orders" = "Buyer's Orders";
"buy_get_free" = "Buy X Get Y";
"buy_x" = "Buy X";
"buy_x_get_free" = "Buy %@ Get %@ Free";
"buff_recharge" = "Buff Recharge";
"buff_income" = "Buff Income";
"buff_explained" = "Buff Explained";
"buff_charge" = "Buff Charge";
"buff_balance" = "Buff Balance";
"buff" = "Buff";
"bronze" = "Bronze";
"alert_title_block" = "Block User";
"block_im_desc" = "Block this user's message";
"block" = "Block";
"birthday" = "Birthday";
"bio" = "Bio";
"binding_successful" = "Binding Successful";
"binding_failed" = "Binding Failed";
"bind_succeed" = "Bind Succeed";
"bind_phone_number" = "Bind Phone Number";
"bind_phone" = "Bind Phone";
"title_bind_epal_account" = "Bind E-Pal Account";
"bind_email" = "Bind Email";
"bind_account" = "Bind Account";
"bind" = "Bind";
"epal_subscription_service_title" = "Better Service, More subscriptions";
"below_x" = "Below %@";
"alert_desc_order_start" = "Before the service begins, please confirm whether you have communicated with your ePal";
"become_epal_title" = "Become an ePal Now!";
"become_an_epal" = "Become an ePal";
"responsiveness_desc" = "Be responsive and don’t miss any orders";
"more_exposure_desc" = "Be proactive to increase the chances of getting orders";
"basic" = "Basic";
"tips_epal_punishment_may_not_response_time" = "Based on this ePal’s recent status, this order may not be responded to on time.";
"banner_personal" = "Banners and Personal Link";
"backgrounds" = "Backgrounds";
"awards" = "Awards";
"avg_im_response_time" = "Avg. IM Response Time";
"average_score" = "Average Score";
"average_order_ratings" = "Average order ratings in the last 7 days";
"average_order_accepting_time" = "Average order accepting time in the last 7 days";
"alert_title_average_order_accepting_time" = "Average order accepting time";
"alert_desc_average_im_response_time4" = "Average IM response time in the last 7 days is less or equal to 5 minutes - 6 Points, between 5 to 10 minutes - 3 Points.";
"average_im_response_time" = "Average IM response time in the last 7 days";
"alert_title_average_im_response_time" = "Average IM response time";
"avatar_desc" = "Avatar must be .JPG, .JPEG or .PNG and cannot exceed 5M.";
"toast_avatar_error_5m" = "Avatar must be .JPG, .JPEG .GIF, or .PNG and cannot exceed 5M.";
"avatar" = "Avatar";
"available_in_x" = "Available in %@";
"available_coupons" = "Available Coupons";
"auto_reply" = "Auto Reply";
"subscribe_term_title" = "Auto renew, cancel anytime";
"auto_renew_enabled" = "Auto Renew Enabled";
"auto_renew_disabled" = "Auto Renew Disabled";
"authorize_your_twitch" = "Authorize your Twitch";
"ask_for" = "Ask For";
"area_code" = "Area Code";
"query_are_you_unblock_user" = "Are you sure you want to unblock this user？";
"alert_desc_double_check" = "Are you sure you want to give up on your effort now?";
"alert_desc_order_delete" = "Are you sure you want to delete this order?";
"alert_desc_order_reject" = "Are you sure you want to decline this order?";
"alert_desc_order_cancel" = "Are you sure you want to cancel this order?";
"alert_desc_delete_topic" = "Are you sure to delete this topic?";
"alert_desc_delete_message" = "Are you sure to delete this message?";
"alert_content_delete_comment" = "Are you sure to delete this comment?";
"alert_desc_delete_comment" = "Are you sure to delete this comment?";
"apply_for_free" = "Apply For Free";
"apply_game_success" = "Application Successful";
"appeal" = "Appeal";
"app_store" = "App Store";
"NSCameraUsageDescription" = "App requires camera permission to take photos and avatars";
"NSPhotoLibraryUsageDescription" = "App requires album permission to set in-app photos and avatars";
"NSUserTrackingUsageDescription" = "App requires access to your device id information.The information will be used for user analytics,app optimization and promotion";
"NSMicrophoneUsageDescription" = "App needs your microphone permission to record audio messages";
"NSAppleMusicUsageDescription" = "App needs to access your media library to provide music playback";
"privacy_music" = "App needs to access your media library to provide music playback";
"alert_desc_legends_what_7_5" = "Master, Apex Predator";
"become_epal_flexible_desc" = "Anytime, Anywhere";
"anonymous_on_leaderboard" = "Anonymous on Leaderboard";
"anonymous_comments" = "Anonymous Comments";
"animated_emojis" = "Animated Emojis";
"all_services" = "All Services";
"all_reviews" = "All Reviews";
"post_rule" = "All posts made should be in accordance with our <Community Guidelines>. Violation of these terms could result in account suspension.";
"all_picture" = "All Picture";
"all_people" = "All People";
"all_games" = "All Games";
"all_followers" = "All Followers";
"all_filter" = "All Filters";
"all" = "All";
"album" = "Album";
"order_refunded_coupon" = "Agreed to refund a coupon";
"order_refunded_buff_coupon_x" = "Agreed to refund %@ Buff and a coupon";
"order_refunded_buff_x" = "Agreed to refund %@ Buff";
"agree" = "Agree";
"age" = "Age";
"alert_desc_after_subscribe" = "After you have subscribed to E-Pal VIP, it might take few minutes for the system to react. Please be patiant.";
"alert_desc_after_recharge" = "After the buff is charged, it may take some time to arrive, please pay attention to the wallet details.";
"my_stream_desc" = "After connecting E-Pal with your Stream, remember to add Panel or Extension as required, otherwise you won’t be eligible for Streamer Conversion Rewards.";
"sign_in_check_agreement_first" = "After checking, you are indicating that you have read and acknowledge the";
"alert_block_other_result" = "After blocking, this person will not be able to interact with you in the community, cannot chat, and cannot place orders";
"additional_requests" = "Additional Requests";
"added" = "ADDED";
"no_social_media_desc" = "Add your social media to the list now!";
"toast_social_limit" = "Add up to 5 social media links";
"add_service_type" = "Add Service Type";
"add_local_music" = "Add Local Music";
"add_link" = "Add Link";
"add_image" = "Add Image";
"add_game_card" = "Add Game Card";
"toast_blocked_success" = "add blocked success";
"add_bio" = "Add Bio";
"add(x)" = "Add (%@)";
"add" = "Add";
"activity_notication" = "Activity Notification";
"active_days" = "Active Days";
"active" = "Active";
"alert_title_activation" = "Activation Successful";
"hide_birthday_desc" = "Activate to stop other users from seeing your birthday.";
"incognito_browsing_desc" = "Activate to browse users’ profiles without a visit notice.";
"achievements" = "Achievements";
"accumulative_subscribers" = "Subscriptions";
"accumulative_income" = "Accumulative Income";
"recharge_time" = "Accumulated monthly recharge";
"account" = "Account";
"alert_desc_comment_less_3h" = "According to your ratings for this service, would you like us to help you out?";
"desc_checkmark_epal_subscribe_auto_renew" = "Accept to renew your subscription with your Buff balance when expiring.";
"accept" = "Accept";
"about_us" = "About Us";
"become_epal_about" = "About E-Pal";
"about" = "About";
"alert_desc_room_block" = "A user cannot enter the room after being blacklisted, please confirm you wish to proceed?";
"skill_exp_desc1" = "A screenshot that clearly shows your game skills";
"notice_title_client_online" = "A regular client just came online";
"notice_title_new_epal" = "A new client just joined E-Pal!";
"cover_exp_desc_3" = "A lot of obstruction on the face. Horrible lighting with a messy background.";
"notice_title_match_epal" = "A client is matching with ePals";
"notice_title_rcm_client" = "A client is looking to order";
"epal_order_more" = "70% more orders";
"cover_rule_desc7" = "7. This rating for your voice line is a review system to improve the overall quality of your store page, and hence removal of potential issues.";
"legends_what_desc_7" = "2. Highly ranked player";
"7_more_draws_if_subscribe_now" = "7 more draws if you Subscribe Now>";
"voice_rule_desc6" = "6. Voice recording must be in English.";
"legends_what_desc_6" = "6. TikTok followers 200K and above";
"cover_rule_desc6" = "6. Excellent is 80 and above, Good is 60 to 79, Moderate is 40 to 59, and Poor is 39 and below;";
"50ev_to_draw" = "50ev to Draw";
"tabke_panel_desc" = "50% more orders";
"panel_desc" = "50% more followers";
"legends_what_desc_5" = "5. YouTube subscribers 200K and above";
"cover_rule_desc5" = "5. Whether if all facial features are clearly defined;";
"voice_rule_desc5" = "5. This rating for your voice line is a review system to improve the overall quality of your store page, and hence removal of potential issues.";
"influencer_drive_desc_5" = "5. Interactions in your video's comment section";
"voice_tips_desc5" = "5. Humour is a great selling point, so tell some jokes if you have any.";
"alert_desc_average_order_ratings" = "5 Stars - 5 Points\n4.5 to 4.9 Stars - 3 Points\nLess than 4.5 Stars - 0 Points";
"5_10_mins" = "5 - 10 mins";
"cover_rule_desc4" = "4. Whether if it is an image of a real person;";
"alert_desc_apply_legends_4" = "4. Your social media accounts that would help us to verify you.";
"legends_what_desc_4" = "4. Social media (e.g. Twitter, Instagram, etc) followers 200K and above";
"influencer_drive_desc_4" = "4. Share your video to other forums & platform, like Reddit etc,.";
"voice_tips_desc4" = "4. It should include your experience, skill and preference in the game, such as “Gold Jungle main”";
"skill_intro_desc4" = "4. If ranking, leaderboards are irrelevant for this game, you could also showcase your skills by uploading your epic gaming moments.";
"my_stream_tips_4" = "4. For more functions, please go to “Settings”";
"voice_rule_desc4" = "4. Excellent is 80 and above, Good is 60 to 79, Moderate is 40 to 59, and Poor is 39 and below;";
"cover_tips_desc4" = "4. Clients overwhelmingly prefer to see pictures of human faces, so avoid using pictures of animals or screenshot of videos and in-game content.";
"30_off_on_orders_subtitle" = "30% off on this ePal’s services. Excluding first order free, or other gifted orders";
"30_off_on_orders" = "30% Off On Orders";
"subscribe_epal_discount" = "30% off on orders";
"cover_tips_desc3" = "3. Your facial features should be clearly-defined in the picture, do not use filters that block off parts of your face;";
"voice_rule_desc3" = "3. Whether you have talked about your in-game skills and/or preferences;";
"cover_rule_desc3" = "3. The lighting of the image;";
"epal_subscription_how_desc_3" = "3. Subscribers will receive notifications when you create rooms and post on Instant and Posts";
"im_limit_tips_3" = "3. Subscribe to this ePal.";
"legends_what_desc_3" = "3. Streamer with 100K and above followers on the streaming platform";
"influencer_drive_desc_3" = "3. Share your video to E-Pal's official social media";
"alert_content_improve_response_time_part3" = "3. Setting up auto-reply could improve customer experiences when you’re not around. Auto-reply does not count towards reply time.";
"voice_tips_desc3" = "3. It should include self-introduction;";
"skill_intro_desc3" = "3. Images/videos and all texts must comply with the E-Pal guidelines and policies. They must also be relevant to E-Pal, ads on E-Pal, or game-related user contributions.";
"my_stream_tips_3" = "3. If you’re streaming on multi-platforms, we will use the signals from the first initiated platform.";
"desc_receive_email_help_3" = "3. If those steps do not fix the issue, please hit “resend” or go back to the previous page and try a different email";
"alert_desc_apply_legends_3" = "3. Your in-game ID";
"become_epal_who_desc_3" = "3. Happy to initiate conversations, helpful and humors. Provide entertainment during orders.";
"empty_desc_potentail_4" = "3. Create a room on Live to gain exposure.";
"twitch_panel_desc_4_epal" = "3. An explicit statement like “Order me on Epal.gg” will improve your click rate";
"twitch_panel_desc_4_user" = "3. An explicit statement like “Find me on Epal.gg” will improve your click rate";
"3_buff_received_need_more_x_play_with_epals" = "3 Buff received. You can top up %@ Buff to place orders with ePals.";
"3_buff_received_play_now_with_epals" = "3 Buff received. You can now place orders with ePals.";
"new_user_send_buff_highlight" = "3 Buff (Worth $3 USD)";
"youtube_share_link_step_2" = "2.Copy the share link in the popup";
"skill_intro_desc2" = "2. You must display some form of game-skill. Level, Rank, Match History, an Ingame Scoreboard, BattlePass level, etc. If you have a rank listed, your screenshot must display your rank.";
"im_limit_tips_2" = "2. Within 3 hours of order completion;";
"voice_rule_desc2" = "2. Whether you have introduced yourself;";
"cover_rule_desc2" = "2. What is in the background, messy or clean;";
"cover_tips_desc2" = "2. Use pictures with clean or designed background;";
"epal_subscription_how_desc_2" = "2. Subscribers are not limited in the number of times they can communicate with you in IM";
"legends_what_desc_2" = "2. Streamer with an average concurrent view of 2,000 and above (past 30-day)";
"twitch_panel_desc_3" = "2. Setup the panel picture and the hyperlink; The link should direct to your E-Pal profile（%@）";
"influencer_drive_desc_2" = "2. Repost your video to E-Pal's POSTS section";
"empty_desc_potentail_3" = "2. Post on Instant to gain exposure.";
"skill_tips_desc2" = "2. Images/videos and caption texts must comply with the guidelines and policies of our platform. They must also be relevant to E-Pal, ads on E-Pal, or game-related user contributions.";
"my_stream_tips_2" = "2. If your streaming platform cannot be shown on E-Pal, please try to reconnect.";
"alert_content_improve_response_time_part2" = "2. If you’re ready to accept orders, please check your notifications regularly. You can always turn on notification sounds in Settings.";
"desc_recive_text_help_2" = "2. If you still can't receive the verification code, you can try to resend or go back to the previous step to change the phone number";
"alert_desc_apply_legends_2" = "2. Your E-Pal ID or Account link,";
"voice_tips_desc2" = "2. Don’t speak too fast nor too slow, make yourself easy to understand;";
"desc_receive_email_help_2" = "2. Check your spam folder";
"epal_subscription_service_desc_2" = "2. Build long-term friendly relationship with customers";
"become_epal_who_desc_2" = "2. Able to provide service in at least 1 category on E-Pal";
"first_order_free" = "1st Order Free";
"epal_subscription_incom_desc_3" = "1000 subscribers = $7990 /month";
"epal_subscription_incom_desc_2" = "100 subscribers = $799/month";
"im_limit_tips_1" = "1.Follow each other;";
"youtube_share_link_step_1" = "1.Click the SHARE button under the video";
"alert_desc_apply_legends_1" = "1. Include the nickname you are commonly known for";
"voice_rule_desc1" = "1. The quality of the audio track, and its background noise;";
"cover_rule_desc1" = "1. The general quality of the image, and its resolution;";
"epal_subscription_how_desc_1" = "1. Subscribers will enjoy a 30% off on all your services, excluding “First Order Free” and “Buy X Get Y” orders";
"influencer_drive_desc_1" = "1. Showcase the best videos here as our top-performing videos";
"skill_intro_desc1" = "1. Screenshots must display information of an account of which you are the sole owner";
"epal_subscription_service_desc_1" = "1. Responsive, Enjoyable, Friendly, Performance";
"voice_tips_desc1" = "1. Record your line in a quiet environment with a decent quality microphone, and try to keep your volume consistent;";
"empty_desc_potentail_2" = "1. Post in the Community and gain exposure.";
"desc_recive_text_help_1" = "1. Please review and confirm that your phone number is spelled correctly";
"desc_receive_email_help_1" = "1. Please review and confirm that your email is spelled correctly";
"skill_tips_desc1" = "1. It's recommended to upload images/videos that showcase and promote yourself.";
"legends_what_desc_1" = "1. Is/was a professional esports player/coach (current or retired)";
"alert_content_improve_response_time_part1" = "1. If you’re busy for any reason, toggle your Online status to: Offline, In an order or Resting. The IM response time won’t be calculated when you set these statuses.";
"cover_tips_desc1" = "1. High resolution pictures with great lighting are always preferred;";
"twitch_panel_desc_2" = "1. Go to your Twitch profile and click “Edit Panels”";
"my_stream_tips_1" = "1. After you connect successfully, E-Pal will automatically sync and show your live room on E-Pal.";
"become_epal_who_desc_1" = "1. 18 years old or above";
"epal_subscription_incom_desc_1" = "1 subscriber = $7.99/month";
"alert_desc_number_of_active_days2" = "1 point for each active day";
"alert_desc_number_of_order_days2" = "1 point for each “Order day”, “Order day” is a days with completed orders";
"one_privilege" = "1 Exposure Privilege.";
"less_5_mins" = "≤ 5 mins";
"greater_10_mins" = "> 10 mins";
"post_rule_highlight" = "<Community Guidelines>";
"free_units_x" = "+%d free units";
"add_more_price" = "+ Add More Service Types";
"buff_explained_1" = "“Buff” is a virtual currency used on E-Pal, it can be used to pay for services and tips. 1.00 Buff = 1.00 USD";
"buff_explained_3" = "“Buff income” Buff earned through providing services.";
"buff_explained_2" = "“Buff balance” is the remaining deposit on your account that could be spent. The money in “Buff balance” is a non-withdrawable currency that can only be spent on the platform.";
"voice_call_[]" = "[Voice Call]";
"system_[]" = "[System]";
"image_[]" = "[image]";
"pertime" = "/Time";
"perhour" = "/Hour";
"pergame" = "/Game";
"per30min" = "/30Min";
"per15min" = "/15Min";
"obtained" = "(Obtained)";
"not_yet_obtained" = "(Not Yet Obtained)";
"10000_influencer" = "%zd+ Influencers";
"years_ago" = "%d years ago";
"weeks_ago" = "%d weeks ago";
"xx_new_messages" = "%d New Messages";
"months_ago" = "%d months ago";
"mins_ago" = "%d mins ago";
"hours_ago" = "%d hours ago";
"days_ago" = "%d days ago";
"influencer_view_comments" = "%@ Views, %@ Comments";
"x_units_total" = "%@ Units total";
"x_buff_to_draw" = "%@ to Draw";
"order_finish_share_title_sweet" = "%@ shared you a promotion link to play %@ [%@] with this nice and sweet ePal. Enjoy %@%%, valid for 7 days, don’t miss out. This promotion can only be used once per user.";
"order_finish_share_title_skilled" = "%@ shared you a promotion link to play %@ [%@] with this highly skilled ePal. Enjoy %@, valid for 7 days, don’t miss out. This promotion can only be used once per user.";
"completed_seller_desc_x" = "%@ remaining for review and refund";
"privilege_exposures_highlight" = "%@ privilege";
"x_photos_in_album" = "%@ photos in album";
"x_or_more" = "%@ or more";
"x_has_won_x" = "%@ has Won %@";
"has_invite_mic_x" = "%@ has been invited to the mic";
"x_buff_coupon" = "%@ Buff Coupon";
"estar2_privilege" = "- eStar 2 Privilege";
"200_to_2000" = "$200 to $2000";
"negative_premium" = "- Premium";
"view_full_image" = "View full image";
"stream_live" = "Live";
"square" = "Square";
"no_live_room_list" = "There is no live stream right now";
"only_epal_user_can_start_live" = "Only ePals can start to stream";
"trends" = "Trends";
"latest" = "Latest";
"gifts" = "Gifts";
"live_or_chat_past_days" = "Streamed in the past 3 days";
"epal_apply_refuse" = "Unable to submit an application because you have been rejected multiple times or do not meet the ePal application requirements";
"sort" = "Sort";
"welcome_to_my_stream_room" = "Welcome to my stream";
"stream_title" = "Room Name";
"stream_title_hint" = "Insert room name";
"stream_cover" = "Stream Cover";
"guests" = "Guests";
"start_stream" = "Start Streaming";
"please_use_real_person_photo" = "Please use an image of a real person as the cover";
"guest_mode_turned_off" = "Guest mode has been turned off";
"toast_internet_reconnection" = "Internet is unstable, reconnecting now";
"toast_internet_cannot_live" = "Internet connection failed, stream has ended";
"toast_internet_anchor_leave" = "This streamer has stepped away, maybe check other streams out";
"toast_internet_check" = "Internet is unstable, please check your network";
"stream_details" = "Stream details";
"announcement" = "Announcement";
"no_information" = "No information";
"inser_announcement" = "Insert Announcement";
"rewarded" = "Rewarded";
"reward_all_fix" = "from";
"update_anno" = "has updated announcement";
"modified_room_name" = "has updated title";
"guest_mode_turned_on" = "has turned on guest mode";
"swap_camera" = "Camera";
"beauty_face" = "Filters";
"gift_effect" = "Special Gift Effects";
"block_list" = "Blacklist";
"stream_stats" = "Stream Stats";
"stream_duration" = "Stream duration";
"unique_viewers" = "Unique viewers";
"stream_turnover" = "Stream turnover";
"alert_room_closed" = "This stream has ended, check out others!";
"toast_internet_reconnection" = "Internet is unstable, reconnecting now";
"host_invite_you_join_mic" = "Host has invited you to join them on Mic";
"set_the_password" = "Set the password";
"about_service" = "About Service";
"close_full_effect" = "Gift effect closed";
"input_steam_name" = "Please fill in a room name";
"upload_steam_cover" = "Please upload a room cover";
"xx_viewers" = "%@ viewers";
"alert_live_break" = "Stream was unexpectedly interrupted";
"alert_live_break_msg" = "Do you want to resume the last stream?";
"alert_live_break_resume" = "Resume stream";
"join" = "Join";
"is_here" = "is here";
"beauty_lightening" = "White";
"beauty_redness" = "Rosy";
"beauty_sharpness" = "Sharp";
"beauty_smoothness" = "Smooth";
"beauty_none" = "None";
"leaderboard_rules" = "Leaderboard Rules";
"x_medals" = "%@'s Medals";
"streaming" = "Streaming";
"available_covers" = "Available Covers";
"video_access_limit" = "Video access has been limited, please go and set up";
"camera_check" = "Please check the availability of your phone's camera";
"cover_setting" = "Cover Setting";
"new_covers" = "New Cover";
"single_word_format_day" = "d";
"single_word_format_hour" = "h";
"single_word_format_minute" = "m";
"toast_guest_switch" = "After enabling the guests, you can allow other users to become guests in the room, and chat with others through video and voice";
"finish_effect" = "After completing this week's entrance effect task, the Entrance Effect will be sent on Monday 00:00 PST. Current progress:";
"room_invite" = "Stream Room Invitation";
"room_invite_desc" = "Accept Stream room and voice room invitations";
"edit_room" = "Edit Room";
"edit_announcement" = "Edit Announcement";
"cover" = "Cover";
"in_dispute" = "In dispute";
"fans_client" = "Follower Client";
"client_desc_fans_tool" = "Influencer Project invited client";
"no_fans_client" = "No follower client";
"the_influencer_project" = "Learn more about Influencer Project >";
"limited" = "limited";
"exposure_priority" = "Exposure Priority";
"store_rating_tips" = "Provide good services to get returning orders";
"store_rating_information" = "Information";
"store_rating_exposure" = "Exposure";
"store_rating_responsiveness" = "Responsiveness";
"store_rating_service" = "Service";
"store_rating_information_desc" = "Complete your information is the first step towards getting orders";
"store_rating_exposure_desc" = "Increased exposure will result in more orders";
"store_rating_responsiveness_desc" = "You need to be responsive to seize the orders you receive";
"store_rating_service_desc" = "Provide a good service so they will come back to order you again";
"service_cover" = "Service Cover";
"voice_introduction" = "Voice Introduction";
"set_up_promotion" = "Set up Promotion";
"set_up_languages" = "Set up Languages";
"add_self_introduction" = "Add Self-Introduction";
"add_pictures_to_album" = "Add Pictures to Album";
"service_cover_qa_title" = "Service Cover Rating";
"service_cover_qa_desc1" = "This is an average between the rating of all your service covers";
"service_cover_rating" = "Cover Rating";
"result" = "Result";
"service_cover_qa_desc2" = "Check more detailed rules when you edit or setup services";
"rating_result" = "Rating result";
"service_cover_qa_desc3" = "The average rating now is";
"voice_introduction_qa_title" = "Voice Introduction Rating";
"voice_introduction_qa_desc1" = "This is an average between the rating of all your service audios";
"voice_introduction_qa_desc3" = "The average rating now is";
"excellent" = "Excellent";
"good" = "Good";
"mediocre" = "Mediocre";
"bad" = "Bad";
"exposure_chats" = "null";
"exposure_match" = "null";
"exposure_live" = "null";
"exposure_posts" = "null";
"exposure_share" = "null";
"chats" = "Chats";
"match_order" = "Match Order";
"exposure_chats_qa" = "Chats through \"My Clients\" In the past 3 days:\n\n1 Rating per 1 Chat，up to 3 ratings";
"exposure_match_qa" = "Match Order through \"My Clients\" in the past 3 days:\n\n1 Rating per successful Order，up to 3 ratings";
"exposure_live_qa" = "Number of Live or Chatroom hosted in the past 3 days:\n\n1 Rating per Live or Chatroom，up to 3 ratings";
"exposure_posts_qa" = "Posts made in the past 3 days:\n\n1 Rating per post，up to 3 ratings";
"exposure_share_qa" = "Profile shares in the past 3 days:\n\n1 Rating per share，up to 3 ratings";
"responsiveness_order" = "Average order accepting time in the past 7 days";
"responsiveness_im" = "Average IM reply time in the past 7 days";
"responsiveness_active" = "Number of active days in the past 7 days";
"order_accepting_time" = "Order Accepting Time";
"reply_time" = "Reply Time";
"responsiveness_order_qa_desc1" = "Orders that falls outside of the range gets 0 rating";
"responsiveness_order_qa_desc2" = "Does not include any order time while your status is \"Gaming, Resting or Offline\"";
"responsiveness_im_qa_desc1" = "Replies that falls outside of the range gets 0 rating";
"responsiveness_im_qa_desc2" = "Does not include any reply time while your status is \"Gaming, Resting or Offline\"";
"responsiveness_active_qa_desc" = "Login to E-Pal will count as \"Active\"";
"service_new_buy" = "The number of new clients who had repurchased 5 or more times in the past 30 days (6 orders including the first order)";
"service_old_buy" = "The number of existing clients who had repurchased 5 or more times in the past 30 days";
"service_subscribers" = "The number of new subscribers you got in the past 30 days";
"service_reward" = "The number of post-order tips you got in the past 30 days";
"service_comment" = "The average review rating of all your orders in the past 30 days";
"repurchased_new_clients" = "Repurchased New Clients";
"repurchased_existing_clients" = "Repurchased Existing Clients";
"order_tips" = "Order Tips";
"review_score" = "Review Score";
"repurchased_clients" = "Repurchased Clients";
"ePal_subscribers" = "ePal Subscribers";
"service_new_buy_desc1" = "New client refers to clients who order you for the first time in the past 3 days, excluding refunded orders";
"service_new_buy_desc2" = "Every order after the first order is considered to be \"repurchase\"";
"service_old_buy_desc1" = "Existing clients means the clients who ordered you for the first time before the past 30 days, excluding refunded orders.";
"service_old_buy_desc2" = "Every order after the first order is considered to be \"repurchase\"";
"service_subscribers_desc1" = "Excluding cancelations";
"service_comment_desc1" = "Excluding orders without ratings";
"pro_player_high_rank_player" = "Pro gamers, high rank players";
"legends_detail_sutitle" = "Officially verified, high exposure and income";
"legends_what_desc_received_prize_or_money" = "3. Have played in notable gaming events and received prize money";
"legends_are_coming" = "Legends are coming!!!";
"supported_games" = "Supported Games";
"legends_what_games_can_apply" = "All non-lifestyle games on E-Pal are supported";
"about_store_rating" = "About Store Rating";
"epal_levels" = "ePal Levels";
"store_rating_and_level_meanings" = "Store Rating and ePal level will decide your exposure, and shows how good you are as an ePal";
"exposure_priority_desc" = "•  Complete ePal tasks to raise store rating\n•  Store rating decides your ePal level\n•  Different levels have different exposures\n";
"service_quality_desc" = "•  Stats show that clients prefer high level ePals\n•  High level also means you provide excellent services, and people are coming back to you";
"rating_update_desc" = "•  Your rating will update in real-time once you complete a task\n•  Level update is slightly slower, it might lag behind the store rating update by few hours";
"service_quality" = "Service Quality";
"rating_update" = "Rating Updates";
"videos" = "Videos";
"rank_requirement" = "Requirements";
"girl_epals" = "Female ePals";
"boy_epals" = "Male ePals";
"legends_epals" = "Legends ePals";
"more_epal" = "More ePals";
"lifestyle_epals" = "Lifestyle ePals";
"gb_epals" = "Female/Male ePals";
"epal_faq" = "ePal FAQ";
"influencer_project" = "Influencer Project";
"legend_verification" = "Legend Verification ";
